[
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Danny Glover", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Brian Cox"
    ], 
    "question": "The films 2012 and The Color Purple feature which American actor, film director and political activist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Pulp Fiction?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Guinea-Bissau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Somalia", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Oman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Seychelles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louisa May Alcott", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Henry James", 
      "Brandon Sanderson", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Herman Melville", 
      "Frank Herbert"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Little Women'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", 
      "Robinson Crusoe"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Chengdu"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "prehistoric metazoans ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "planets and solar systems; more commonly called Planetary science", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "religion"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleozoology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lyon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lugdunum' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "I Love Lucy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Brady Bunch", 
      "Sanford and Son", 
      "My Favourite Martian"
    ], 
    "question": "What popular US TV sitcom With 3 Words made its first appearance in 1951 & ran until 1957?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aristotle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plato", 
      "Socrates", 
      "Diogenes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who taught Alexander the Great? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard III", 
      "Othello", 
      "Macbeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Shakespeare's first play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dolphin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Lion", 
      "Gorilla"
    ], 
    "question": "Apart From Humans There Is Only One Other Creature That Has Sex For Pleasure. What is it? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cricket", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "The Duckworth Lewis Method Is Used To Keep The Score In Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bradley Cooper", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Russell Crowe"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Alias and American Hustle feature which American actor, filmmaker and singer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed X-Men: Apocalypse?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Belize?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "People's Republic of China", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Laos", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Oman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Nepal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Hound of the Baskervilles'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Two Towers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Last Battle"
    ], 
    "question": "'Aragorn sped on up the hill.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the largest island in the Caribbean?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "race", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "parasites", 
      "in ethics, duty", 
      "rocks", 
      "grasses", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ethnology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rauma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lappi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Blues Brothers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sister Act", 
      "National Lampoon's Vacation", 
      "Animal House"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Comedy Film Does Aretha Franklin Star As A Proprietress Of A Soul Food Joint? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Declaration Of Independence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Constitution", 
      "The Emancipation Procalation", 
      "The Liberty Decree"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 1776 American Affirmation Asserted The Basic Rights Of All?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Hardy", 
      "James Joyce", 
      "Emily Bront\u00eb", 
      "George Elliot"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"A Christmas Carol\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tomato", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Garlic", 
      "Onion", 
      "Chili Pepper"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Alicante A Variety Of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ewan McGregor", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Downey Jr.", 
      "Robin Williams", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "George Clooney", 
      "Laurence Fishburne", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Brad Pitt", 
      "James Franco", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British actor has starred in films including Beauty and the Beast and Star Wars: Episode I \u2013 The Phantom Menace?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Apocalypse Now?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Cape Verde is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Montenegro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Romania", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Malta", 
      "Italy", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Austria", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Poland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Albania?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Mann", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Cassandra Clare", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Karel \u010capek", 
      "Ayn Rand"
    ], 
    "question": "Which German novelist, and 1929 Nobel Prize laureate wrote 'Buddenbrooks (1909 Deutsche Buchgemeinschaft ed.)'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Man in the High Castle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nineteen Eighty-Four", 
      "Brave New World", 
      "The Road", 
      "Blindness", 
      "1Q84", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Atlas Shrugged"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1962, which piece of written work starts with the line 'For a week Mr. R. Childan had been anxiously watching the mail. But the valuable shipment from the Rocky Mountain States had not arrived. As he opened up his store on Friday morning and saw only letters on the floor by the mail slot he thought, I\u2019m going to have an angry customer.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madrid\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lisbon", 
      "Paris", 
      "Rome"
    ], 
    "question": "Which European capital city stands on the Manzanares River?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "methods", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "fungi", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "myths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Apiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "\u0130zmir", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Istanbul", 
      "Ankara", 
      "Bursa", 
      "Edirne", 
      "Trabzon", 
      "Adana", 
      "Sivas", 
      "Antalya", 
      "Konya", 
      "Kayseri"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Smyrna?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chevy Chase", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "Tom Hanks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oklahoma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Missouri", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Macbeth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romeo & Juliette", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "Double, double toil and trouble, Fire burn, and cauldron bubble. Comes from which of Shakespeare's plays?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Campanulate", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clochical", 
      "Cambarn", 
      "Belieux"
    ], 
    "question": "What Word Is Used To Describe Bell Shaped Flowers?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Oche", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Div", 
      "The Par", 
      "The Sod"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is the Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Frances Fisher"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Gravity and Speed feature which American actress and producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Lesotho is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "People's Republic of China shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Carrie' was written by which American author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Twist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Germinal", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "'Among other public buildings in a certain town, which for many reasons it will be prudent to refrain from mentioning, and to which I will assign no fictitious name, there is one anciently common to most towns, great or small: to wit, a workhouse; and in this workhouse was born; on a day and date which I need not trouble myself to repeat, inasmuch as it can be of no possible consequence to the' This is the first line of which 1839 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Singapore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Taipei", 
      "Kuala Lumpur", 
      "Malacca"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Singapore?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "underground water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "Tibet", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows", 
      "the hind regions (rectum, anus, colon and pelvic floor) of the body", 
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
      "the nature of Buddha", 
      "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Hydrogeology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alavus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called T\u00f6ys\u00e4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "George I", 
      "Henry VI", 
      "Richard III", 
      "Charles II"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the father of Elizabeth I?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The City & the City", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Thorin' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Feet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Backs", 
      "Teeth", 
      "Knees"
    ], 
    "question": "What Does A Chiropodist Treat", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cricket", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "The Duckworth Lewis Method Is Used To Keep The Score In Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Robbins", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Mystic River and Top Gun feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Solo: A Star Wars Story?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Antigua and Barbuda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gabon", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Niger", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Benin", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Angola", 
      "Eritrea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Central African Republic?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "George R. R. Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'A Feast for Crows' was written by which American writer, screenwriter and television producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Great Gatsby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Shining", 
      "The Silmarillion", 
      "American Psycho (book)", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "The Trial"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'In my younger and more vulnerable years my father gave me some advice that I\u2019ve been turning over in my mind ever since.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "San Francisco", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York City", 
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "Baltimore"
    ], 
    "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "symptoms", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "waves or wave motions", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Biogeomorphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Akashi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'\u014ckubo' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Reginald Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Wayne Gacey Jr", 
      "Ted Bundy", 
      "Ed Gaine"
    ], 
    "question": "Which notorious murderer, hanged in July 1953, had his story told in the film \"Ten Rillington Place\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John F Kennedy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "Malcolm X", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard III", 
      "Othello", 
      "Macbeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Shakespeare's first play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Crash", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Loom", 
      "A Brush", 
      "A Forest"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Collective Name For Rhinoceroses?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Evander Holyfield", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson", 
      "Oscar De La Hoya", 
      "Floyd Mayweather"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Heavweight Boxer Was Known As The Real Deal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Glenn Close", 
      "Reese Witherspoon", 
      "Melissa Leo", 
      "Frances Conroy", 
      "Jennifer Aniston", 
      "Drew Barrymore", 
      "Uma Thurman", 
      "Cameron Diaz", 
      "Amy Adams", 
      "Laura Linney"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Gosford Park and Mission: Impossible feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Brunei?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "North Korea", 
      "Palau", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Singapore"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Japan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Suzanne Collins", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Kurt Vonnegut", 
      "Ayn Rand"
    ], 
    "question": "'Catching Fire' was written by which American television writer and novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Women", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Candide", 
      "The Neverending Story"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1868, which piece of written work starts with the line ''Christmas won't be Christmas without any presents''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prague\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "St Petersberg", 
      "Oxford", 
      "Vienna"
    ], 
    "question": "Which European city is nicknamed \"The city of a hundred spires\" and has tourist attractions including St Vitus Cathedral and Charles Bridge?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "puzzles", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine", 
      "cats", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "forms that is used in several other fields (biology, linguistics, astronomy, etc", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "enzymes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Urology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "\u014ctsu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Sakamoto?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tracy Ullman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vanessa Phillips", 
      "Paula Skeeberg", 
      "Mary Myers"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southampton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cardiff", 
      "Portsmouth", 
      "Plymouth"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Did The Mayflower Set Sail From In 1620?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Macbeth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romeo & Juliette", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "Double, double toil and trouble, Fire burn, and cauldron bubble. Comes from which of Shakespeare's plays?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Newton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Pascal", 
      "Ohm"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The SI Unit Of Force", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Evander Holyfield", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson", 
      "Oscar De La Hoya", 
      "Floyd Mayweather"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Heavweight Boxer Was Known As The Real Deal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Billy Bob Thornton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Colin Firth"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor, filmmaker, singer, songwriter, and musician has starred in films including Armageddon and Love Actually?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Lucia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Latvia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "India", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Thailand"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Russia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hans Christian Andersen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beatrix Potter", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Astrid Lindgren", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Johannes V. Jensen", 
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Agatha Christie"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Wild Swans'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dracula", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "'Salem's Lot", 
      "Carrie", 
      "World War Z", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "I Am Legend"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1897, which piece of written work starts with the line '3 May. Bistritz. - Left Munich at 8.35 p.m. on 1st May, arriving at Vienna early next Morning; should have arrived at 6.46, but train was an hour late.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Copenhagen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Viborg", 
      "Amsterdam", 
      "Stockholm"
    ], 
    "question": "The Little Mermaid is found in the harbour of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the field of medicine that deals with the skin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "birds", 
      "parasites", 
      "the ancient Egyptians", 
      "the Sun", 
      "glaciers", 
      "a set of words and/or phrases, usually in relation to some particular canon or field of study", 
      "Semitic cultures", 
      "childbirth, sometimes spelled"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dermatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Maebashi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Haga' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pennsylvania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ohio", 
      "Maryland", 
      "Delaware"
    ], 
    "question": "In which American state is George A. Romero's 1968 film 'Night Of The Living Dead' set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John F Kennedy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "Malcolm X", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Van Gogh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salvador Dali", 
      "Andy Warhol", 
      "Raphael", 
      "Vermeer"
    ], 
    "question": "Which painter reputedly cut of his own ear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Opossum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel", 
      "Coyote", 
      "Otter"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "3,000 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10,000 Metres", 
      "5,000 Metres", 
      "8,000 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Affleck", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice and Suicide Squad feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed X-Men: Days of Future Past?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Guinea-Bissau?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "United States of America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "India", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Thailand"
    ], 
    "question": "Russia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "William Shakespeare", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "Isaac Newton", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Lee Child", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "J. K. Rowling"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English playwright and poet wrote 'The Merchant of Venice'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Neville Longbottom' appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dracula", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "'Salem's Lot", 
      "Carrie", 
      "World War Z", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "I Am Legend"
    ], 
    "question": "'3 May. Bistritz. - Left Munich at 8.35 p.m. on 1st May, arriving at Vienna early next Morning; should have arrived at 6.46, but train was an hour late.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Brussels-Capital Region"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Belgium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or exploration of caves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "methods", 
      "methods", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "glaciers", 
      "cancer", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Speleology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fuch\u016b", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nishifu?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tracy Ullman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vanessa Phillips", 
      "Paula Skeeberg", 
      "Mary Myers"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lithography", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Embography", 
      "Calligraphy", 
      "Recography"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the art of tracing designs and making impressions of them called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Es", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El", 
      "En", 
      "Ei"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for einsteinium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fourteen", 
      "Thirteen", 
      "Twelve"
    ], 
    "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Richard Burton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aaron Paul", 
      "Mark Hamill", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Peter O'Toole", 
      "Burt Reynolds", 
      "Mickey Rooney", 
      "Michael Ironside", 
      "Joaquin Phoenix", 
      "Eric Roberts"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Cleopatra and Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? feature which Welsh actor (1925-1984)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Apollo 13?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Federated States of Micronesia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Monaco", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Italy", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Germany", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "United Kingdom", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Austria", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Malta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Andorra?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone' was written by which British novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ulysses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "Lolita", 
      "The Brothers Karamazov", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias"
    ], 
    "question": "'Stately, plump Buck Mulligan came from the stairhead, bearing a bowl of lather on which a mirror and a razor lay crossed.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Australia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Madagascar"
    ], 
    "question": "Which island country lies to the East of Mauritius?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes", 
      "primates", 
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere", 
      "existence", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections", 
      "character", 
      "living tissues"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phlebology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kouvola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Jaala?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michelangelo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leonardo", 
      "Raphael", 
      "Donatello"
    ], 
    "question": "By what name is the great italian sculptor & artist Buonarroti better known?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shark", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Whale", 
      "Dolphin", 
      "Orca"
    ], 
    "question": "The fins of what sea creature are made into a soup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "An Ice Skating Rink", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Football Pitch", 
      "A Tennis Court", 
      "A Rugby Pitch"
    ], 
    "question": "In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Ironside", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Mickey Rooney", 
      "Stephen Fry", 
      "Kenneth Branagh", 
      "Sam Elliott", 
      "Tom Waits", 
      "Tim Curry", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Peter Cushing"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Canadian actor, producer, screenwriter, director, editor and playwright has starred in films including Smallville and Castle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Sin City?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Suriname is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North Korea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Philippines", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Palau", 
      "Laos", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Nepal", 
      "East Timor"
    ], 
    "question": "South Korea shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "C. S. Lewis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Douglas Adams", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "H. G. Wells"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British writer wrote 'The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sense and Sensibility", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Candide", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Manon Lescaut", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'The family of Dashwood had been long settled in Sussex.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Riyadh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mecca", 
      "Medina", 
      "Jeddah"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Saudi Arabia ?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "methods", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "fungi", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "myths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Apiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Salo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called S\u00e4rkisalo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spilled champagne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A lightning strike", 
      "Divine intervention", 
      "A plutonium power core"
    ], 
    "question": "What caused the computer in Electric Dreams to become alive?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Geronimo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poundmaker", 
      "Sitting Bull", 
      "Sequoyah"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the last of the apache warrior chiefs", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michelangelo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Edvard Much", 
      "Leonardo da Vinci", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "Who painted \"The Creation Of Adam\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Heart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul", 
      "Blood"
    ], 
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shigeru Miyamoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yu Suzuki", 
      "Satoru Iwata", 
      "Gunpei Yokoi"
    ], 
    "question": "Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Affleck", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Suicide Squad and Argo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of The Bahamas is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sierra Leone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Niger", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guinea?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Final Problem'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince"
    ], 
    "question": "'The villagers of Little Hangleton still called it \"the Riddle House\" even though it has been many years since the Riddle family had lived there.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madrid\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lisbon", 
      "Paris", 
      "Rome"
    ], 
    "question": "Which European capital city stands on the Manzanares River?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "bacteria", 
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations", 
      "the moon", 
      "dragonflies and damselflies", 
      "plankton", 
      "the study or skill of preparing mixed drinks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Demography the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pori", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio", 
      "Porvoo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Noormarkku' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tracy Ullman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vanessa Phillips", 
      "Paula Skeeberg", 
      "Mary Myers"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dog", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horse", 
      "Goat", 
      "Ghost"
    ], 
    "question": "The only __________ to ever appear in a Shakespearean play was Crab in \"The Two Gentlemen of Verona.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stork", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pelican", 
      "Flamingo", 
      "Swan"
    ], 
    "question": "The shoebill __________, native to Africa, is often compared to a statue. The bird will stand perfectly still for long periods waiting for fish to come to surface in the water.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Butterfly", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dragonfly", 
      "Mayfly", 
      "Horsefly"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Swimming Stroke Was Introduced Into Competition In 1952", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Clooney", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including ER and Gravity?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Kiribati?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Suriname", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "United Kingdom", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Austria", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders France?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Night Shift'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Australia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "India", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "In which country would you find Uluru?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "mountains and their mapping", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "cats", 
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "a neologism for the Pilates method, a system of physical exercise", 
      "nerves", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Orology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Varkaus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Kangaslampi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hawaii", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alaska", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "What Became America's 50th State On August 21st 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Miller", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "William Johnson", 
      "Arnold Clark", 
      "Fred George"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US dramatist was once married to Marylin Monroe and penned the plays \"Death Of A Salesman\" and \"The Crucible\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formicary", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Insectabode", 
      "Tellenite", 
      "Anobide"
    ], 
    "question": "Where do ants live?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blackburn Rovers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Manchester United", 
      "Arsenal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which was the second club to win the English Premier League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Ryan Reynolds"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Titanic and Inception feature which American actor and film producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Cameron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Titanic?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Lucia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kazakhstan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pakistan", 
      "Iran", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Oman", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "India", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Uzbekistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Newton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Daniel Defoe", 
      "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "William Shakespeare", 
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio", 
      "Charles Darwin"
    ], 
    "question": "'Opticks, or a Treatise of the Reflections, Refractions, Inflections and Colours of Light' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.' This is the first line of which 2007 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mogadishu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timbuktu", 
      "Bakar", 
      "Addis Ababa"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Somalia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "algae", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "minerals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "animals"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Algology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Orimattila", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Artj\u00e4rvi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Constantinople", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Istanbul", 
      "New Constantinople"
    ], 
    "question": "To What Was Byzantium Renamed In 330 AD?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lead & Tin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Copper & Iron", 
      "Copper & Lead", 
      "Iron & Tin"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Alloy Pewter Made From", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "England"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Laurence Fishburne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Award-winning American film, theatre, and television actor, film director, film producer, and playwright has starred in films including The Matrix and Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of X2?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Bahrain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mauritania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Niger", 
      "Portugal", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cameroon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Senegal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "G. K. Chesterton"
    ], 
    "question": "'Partners in Crime' was written by which English mystery and detective writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 2007, which piece of written work starts with the line 'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Copenhagen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Viborg", 
      "Amsterdam", 
      "Stockholm"
    ], 
    "question": "The Little Mermaid is found in the harbour of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "angels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "numbers", 
      "religion", 
      "Semitic cultures", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "the Assyrians", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Angelology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "N\u00eemes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nemausus?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles II", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "James II", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rembrandt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vermeer", 
      "Van Gogh", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Virgil Grissom ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yuri Gagarin", 
      "Alan Shepard", 
      "Neil Armstrong"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the first man to go to space twice?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Ryder Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The FIFA World Cup", 
      "The UEFA Champion's League", 
      "The America's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "The Solheim Cup Is The Woman's Equivalent Of Which Famous Sporting Cup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Quinn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Hong", 
      "Gary Cooper", 
      "Sam Shepard", 
      "Terry Crews", 
      "Kevin Bacon", 
      "Jon Bernthal", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Bill Hader", 
      "Paul Newman", 
      "Simon Pegg"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including La Strada and Zorba the Greek?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of A Beautiful Mind?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Antigua and Barbuda is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Djibouti", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Israel", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus"
    ], 
    "question": "Sudan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Joyce", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Samuel Beckett", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Finnegans Wake' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gone with the Wind", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fall of the King", 
      "All Quiet on the Western Front", 
      "A Tale of Two Cities", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Scarlett O\u2019Hara was not beautiful, but men seldom realized it when caught by her charm as the Tarleton twins were.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mojave", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sonoran", 
      "Arizonan", 
      "Baja"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the desert located in South East California.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "microorganisms", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure of cells", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "the process of biological evolution", 
      "children's behavior and development", 
      "minerals", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "eggs", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Microbiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Savonlinna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Kerim\u00e4ki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Walter Raleigh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sir Francis Drake", 
      "James Cook", 
      "Ernest Shackleton"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Brought Back Tobacco And Potatoes From The Americas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pre-Raphaelite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neo-Raphaelite", 
      "Pre-Jacobian", 
      "Neo-Jacobian"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of English painters formed in 1848. These artists attempted to recapture an old style of painting. They rejected industrialized England and focused on painting from nature, producing detailed, colorful works. What were they called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Central America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Africa", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Japan"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Is The Natural Habitat Of The Cheese Plant?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Pineapple", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Strawberry", 
      "An Apple", 
      "A Raspberry"
    ], 
    "question": "What Type Of Fruit Is Depicted On Top Of The Men's Singles Trophy At Wimbledon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charlize Theron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Keira Knightley"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Mad Max: Fury Road and Prometheus?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed The Godfather Part II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Bhutan is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "East Timor", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Japan", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "Indonesia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Marquis de Sade", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nikolai Gogol", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Voltaire", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Stanis\u0142aw Lem", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Agatha Christie"
    ], 
    "question": "'The 120 Days of Sodom' was written by which novelist and philosopher?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frankenstein", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cloud Atlas", 
      "Coraline", 
      "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Gulliver's Travels", 
      "Flowers for Algernon", 
      "World War Z"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1818, which piece of written work starts with the line 'You will rejoice to hear that no disaster has accompanied the commencement of an enterprise which you have regarded with such evil forebodings.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Canada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "United States of America", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Cuba", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Honduras"
    ], 
    "question": "__________ is home to the world's most remote weather station. Its Eureka weather station is 600 miles from the North Pole.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure of cells", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "museum management", 
      "earthquakes", 
      "mollusks", 
      "the moon", 
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Economic geology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saarij\u00e4rvi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Pylk\u00f6nm\u00e4ki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Reginald Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Wayne Gacey Jr", 
      "Ted Bundy", 
      "Ed Gaine"
    ], 
    "question": "Which notorious murderer, hanged in July 1953, had his story told in the film \"Ten Rillington Place\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Francis Drake", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horatio Nelson", 
      "George Rodney", 
      "John Jervis"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Played Bowls Before Engaging The Spanish Armada?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Bleak House", 
      "Wuthering Heights"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Mr Bennet' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Centipedes And Millipedes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Crabs and Lobsters", 
      "Slugs and Snails", 
      "Scorpions and Spiders"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these pairs are Myriapods?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formula One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Cricket", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "Monza & Silverstone Are Venues For Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shah Rukh Khan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlton Heston", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Jack Nicholson", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Harry Dean Stanton", 
      "Danny Trejo", 
      "Dustin Hoffman", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Devdas and Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham... feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martin Scorsese", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Gangs of New York?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Mauritius is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brazil", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "United Kingdom", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Austria", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "France shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stendhal", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Octave Mirbeau", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Guy de Maupassant", 
      "Anatole France", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Victor Hugo", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Albert Camus", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Red and the Black' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Man in the High Castle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nineteen Eighty-Four", 
      "Brave New World", 
      "The Road", 
      "Blindness", 
      "1Q84", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Atlas Shrugged"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1962, which piece of written work starts with the line 'For a week Mr. R. Childan had been anxiously watching the mail. But the valuable shipment from the Rocky Mountain States had not arrived. As he opened up his store on Friday morning and saw only letters on the floor by the mail slot he thought, I\u2019m going to have an angry customer.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salt", 
      "Foliage", 
      "Human Settlement"
    ], 
    "question": "Over 75% of the Earth's surface is covered by some form of _____.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the attribute (of a word) of being self descriptive", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "the medical study of the causation of disease", 
      "mental processes in living creatures", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
      "dialects", 
      "vocal sounds"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Autology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saint-Denis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "'La Chapelle' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1805", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1863", 
      "1911", 
      "1840"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Was The Battle Of Trafalgar Fought?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Hardy", 
      "James Joyce", 
      "Emily Bront\u00eb", 
      "George Elliot"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"A Christmas Carol\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Earwig", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ant", 
      "Praying Mantis", 
      "Woodlouse"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Insect Has A Pair Of Prominent Pincers At The Tip Of It's Abdomen?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Foreman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joe Frazier", 
      "Wilfredo Gomez", 
      "Roberto Duran"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did Muhammed Ali Fight In 'The Rumble In The Jungle''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Hader", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Star Wars Episode VII: The Force Awakens and The BFG?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Brunei is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Liberia", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Equatorial Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Mali?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Philip Pullman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "William Shakespeare", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Salman Rushdie", 
      "George Orwell"
    ], 
    "question": "'His Dark Materials trilogy' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Return of the King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Hobbit"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pippin looked out from the shelter of Gandalf's coat.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Washington DC", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "San Francisco"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of The United States?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "minerals", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "disease classification", 
      "water", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "lightning", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dendrochronology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Takamatsu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Sagita' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rembrandt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vermeer", 
      "Van Gogh", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Smallpox", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Infuenza", 
      "COVID-19", 
      "Rubella"
    ], 
    "question": "What Vaccine Did Edward Jenner Develop? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nigeria", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Senegal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Did Chelsea Striker Didier Drogba Represent At International Level?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brad Pitt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christopher Lee", 
      "Christian Bale"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Dallas and Inglourious Basterds feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Burton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Batman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "San Marino is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkmenistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Georgia", 
      "Syria", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Israel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Iran?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "James Fenimore Cooper", 
      "Donna Leon", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Cassandra Clare"
    ], 
    "question": "Which novelist and screenwriter from the United States wrote 'The Great Gatsby'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Return of the King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Hobbit"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1955, which piece of written work starts with the line 'Pippin looked out from the shelter of Gandalf's coat.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rushmore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yellowstone", 
      "Everest", 
      "Fairweather"
    ], 
    "question": "On what mountain are four presidents' faces carved? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the climate", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "glaciers", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "lightning", 
      "life in outer space", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "fish"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Climatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ramat Gan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Tel Aviv", 
      "Haifa", 
      "Petah Tikva", 
      "Beersheba", 
      "Rishon LeZion", 
      "Rehovot", 
      "Netanya", 
      "Herzliya", 
      "Acre"
    ], 
    "question": "'Jarisha' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Blues Brothers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sister Act", 
      "National Lampoon's Vacation", 
      "Animal House"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Comedy Film Does Aretha Franklin Star As A Proprietress Of A Soul Food Joint? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ray Bradbury", 
      "Joseph Heller", 
      "Harper Lee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"The Great Gatsby\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What color spots has the common ladybird?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nintendo Entertainment System", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Natural Emitting Screen", 
      "Near Energy Source"
    ], 
    "question": "What does the acronym \"NES\" stand for?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elizabeth Banks", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Naomi Watts"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Modern Family and The Hunger Games feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of The Dark Knight?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The Bahamas is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Niger", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Malta", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Italy", 
      "France", 
      "Benin", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Togo", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Nigeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Algeria shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Newton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Daniel Defoe", 
      "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "William Shakespeare", 
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio", 
      "Charles Darwin"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Opticks, or a Treatise of the Reflections, Refractions, Inflections and Colours of Light'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The A.B.C. Murders", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "Lolita", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "American Psycho (book)", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Crime and Punishment"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1936, which piece of written work starts with the line 'It was in June of 1935 that I came home from my ranch in South America for a stay of about six months.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Australia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Madagascar"
    ], 
    "question": "Which island country lies to the East of Mauritius?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "men", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "stalkers", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "fish", 
      "the study and interpretation of symbols, or a set of symbols", 
      "weather", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "dogs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dudology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fuji", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takaoka' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "King Lear", 
      "Julius Caesar", 
      "Othello", 
      "Coriolanus", 
      "Anthony and Cleopatra"
    ], 
    "question": "In which Shakespearean tragedy Does Laertes appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "How many beams of light are used to record a holograph?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vince", 
      "Erika", 
      "Commander Cole"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is the first gym leader you fight in 'Pok\u00e9mon' for the Game Boy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Wayne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Hugh Jackman"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Longest Day and Stagecoach feature which American actor (1907\u20131979)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Home Alone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Trinidad and Tobago?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fiji", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nauru", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Kiribati", 
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Palau", 
      "East Timor", 
      "New Zealand", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Japan", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Vietnam"
    ], 
    "question": "Solomon Islands shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scottish physician and author wrote 'The Man with the Twisted Lip'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Return of the King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Hobbit"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Pippin looked out from the shelter of Gandalf's coat.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bamako", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dakar", 
      "Accra", 
      "Kumasi"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Mali?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "crop circles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "sex", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "shells and of molluscs", 
      "China", 
      "classification", 
      "lightning"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cereology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "\u0130zmir", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Istanbul", 
      "Ankara", 
      "Bursa", 
      "Edirne", 
      "Trabzon", 
      "Adana", 
      "Sivas", 
      "Antalya", 
      "Konya", 
      "Kayseri"
    ], 
    "question": "'Smyrna' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chevy Chase", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "Tom Hanks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Submarine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Torpedo", 
      "TNT", 
      "The Tank"
    ], 
    "question": "Designed By Robert Fulton, Which Weapon Was Tested In The Seine In 1801?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Water Babies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oliver Twist", 
      "The Little Prince", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous book contains the line \"Once upon a time there was a little chimney sweep and his name was Tom\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Borneo & Sumatra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bali & Lombok", 
      "Sulawesi & Java", 
      "New Guinea & Komodo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 2 Islands Are The Natural Habitat Of The Orang-Utan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Six", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Eight", 
      "Two"
    ], 
    "question": "How many pockets does a snooker table have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Amy Adams", 
      "Uma Thurman", 
      "Cameron Diaz", 
      "Drew Barrymore", 
      "Jennifer Aniston", 
      "Elizabeth Banks", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Charlize Theron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Volver and All About My Mother?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ridley Scott", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Gladiator?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Brunei is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malaysia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Japan", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "Indonesia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Umberto Eco", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Orhan Pamuk", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Jos\u00e9 Saramago", 
      "Paulo Coelho", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wuthering Heights", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Shining", 
      "The Phantom of the Opera", 
      "Coraline", 
      "Carmilla", 
      "The Picture of Dorian Gray", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "'Salem's Lot", 
      "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde"
    ], 
    "question": "'1801\u2014I have just returned from a visit to my landlord\u2014the solitary neighbour that I shall be troubled with.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gambia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Namibia"
    ], 
    "question": "Banjul is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ends or final causes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "ticks and mites", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "mental processes in living creatures", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "human beings killing other human beings", 
      "the study of picture postcards"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Teleology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Naples", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Milan", 
      "Florence", 
      "Turin", 
      "Venice", 
      "Genoa", 
      "Bologna", 
      "Palermo", 
      "Padua", 
      "Trieste"
    ], 
    "question": "'Neapolis' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jingle All The Way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Santa Clause", 
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "Bad Santa"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Popular Christmas Movie Featured A Must Have Toy Called 'Turbo Man''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Expressionism", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Realism", 
      "Impressionism", 
      "Fauvism"
    ], 
    "question": "Which term refers to art that uses emphasis and distortion to communicate emotion?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colour Blindness", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Short Sightedness", 
      "Far Sightedness", 
      "Cataracts"
    ], 
    "question": "Which sight problem occurs in men far more than in women?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "3,000 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10,000 Metres", 
      "5,000 Metres", 
      "8,000 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Affleck", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice and Suicide Squad feature which American film actor, director and screenwriter?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Inception?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Andorra is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Federated States of Micronesia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Japan", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Laos", 
      "Nauru", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Australia", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Kiribati"
    ], 
    "question": "Palau shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vladimir Nabokov", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Kurt Vonnegut", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Thomas Mann", 
      "Herman Melville", 
      "Frank Herbert", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Nikolai Gogol"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Russian-American novelist, lepidopterist, professor wrote 'The Annotated Lolita (1991 Vintage Books ed.)'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The City & the City", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mr Utterson the lawyer was a man of a rugged countenance, that was never lighted by a smile; cold, scanty and embarrassed in discourse; backward in sentiment; lean, long, dusty, dreary and yet somehow lovable.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ulaanbaatar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uliastai", 
      "Khovd", 
      "Ulaangom"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Mongolia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "gemstones and ornamental materials", 
      "in ethics, duty", 
      "lightning", 
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "the Shroud of Turin", 
      "writing systems", 
      "the liver; a branch of medicine", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Fungology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tokushima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Okinosu?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pennsylvania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ohio", 
      "Maryland", 
      "Delaware"
    ], 
    "question": "In which American state is George A. Romero's 1968 film 'Night Of The Living Dead' set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uganda", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Kenya"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did Idi Amin invade in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ray Bradbury", 
      "Joseph Heller", 
      "Harper Lee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"The Great Gatsby\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albatross", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bald Eagle", 
      "Perigrine Falcon", 
      "Ostrich"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Bird Has The Largest Wingspan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Oche", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Div", 
      "The Par", 
      "The Sod"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is the Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Faye Dunaway", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas"
    ], 
    "question": "The films CSI: Crime Scene Investigation and Chinatown feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed X-Men: Apocalypse?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Tuvalu?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rwanda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burundi", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Chad", 
      "Angola", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Mozambique"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Uganda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alice Munro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Margaret Atwood", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola"
    ], 
    "question": "'Selected Stories (Munro)' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cambodia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thailand", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Laos", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Philippines"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country is the Mekong River Delta", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the kidneys and their diseases, a branch of medicine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "heat", 
      "bees", 
      "sacred texts", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "blood serum", 
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "disease classification", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Nephrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "New York City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "Baltimore", 
      "Seattle", 
      "Indianapolis"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called New Amsterdam?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hoover", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin", 
      "Roosevelt", 
      "Johnson"
    ], 
    "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jonathan Swift", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "William Godwin", 
      "Voltaire", 
      "Henry Fielding"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Gullivers Travels\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Voice box", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tongue", 
      "Tonsils", 
      "Throat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the common name for the larynx?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Croquet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Badminton", 
      "Billiards"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Game Makes Use Of Hoops", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kevin Costner", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Keanu Reeves"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor and filmmaker has starred in films including Man of Steel and The Untouchables?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Batman Begins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Comoros", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mauritius", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Burundi", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Namibia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Madagascar?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Full Dark, No Stars'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "Sancho Panza appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Clockwork Orange", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?", 
      "Slaughterhouse-Five", 
      "We", 
      "Brave New World", 
      "L'Ing\u00e9nu", 
      "Animal Farm", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The City & the City"
    ], 
    "question": "'\u201cWhat's it going to be then, eh?\u201d There was me, that is Alex, and my three droogs, that is Pete, Georgie, and Dim, Dim being really dim, and we sat in the Korova Milkbar making up our rassoodocks what to do with the evening, a flip dark chill winter bastard though dry.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Burkina Faso", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Mali", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Sierra Leone"
    ], 
    "question": "Ouagadougou is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "origin of life", 
      "earthquakes", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "study of devil worshipers", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
      "algae", 
      "enzymes", 
      "music"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Helioseismology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lisbon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Porto", 
      "Coimbra", 
      "Funchal", 
      "Braga", 
      "Angra do Hero\u00edsmo", 
      "Set\u00fabal", 
      "Guimar\u00e3es", 
      "Ponta Delgada", 
      "\u00c9vora", 
      "Viseu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Olisipo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Clarence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Terrence", 
      "Horace", 
      "Boris"
    ], 
    "question": "In the 1946 film, It's a Wonderful Life, what's the name of George Bailey's guardian angel?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dallas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Austin", 
      "Houston"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Was John F Kennedy Assassinated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michelangelo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Edvard Much", 
      "Leonardo da Vinci", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "Who painted \"The Creation Of Adam\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What color spots has the common ladybird?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Liam Neeson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Samuel L. Jackson", 
      "Robert De Niro", 
      "Bruce Willis", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "William Shatner", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Dan Aykroyd"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Sesame Street and Gangs of New York feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roland Emmerich", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Independence Day?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Eswatini is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Friedrich Engels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Ende", 
      "Erich Maria Remarque", 
      "Karl May", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Communist Manifesto'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The City & the City", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders"
    ], 
    "question": "'Mr Utterson the lawyer was a man of a rugged countenance, that was never lighted by a smile; cold, scanty and embarrassed in discourse; backward in sentiment; lean, long, dusty, dreary and yet somehow lovable.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Etna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vesuvius", 
      "Amiata", 
      "Pico"
    ], 
    "question": "What volcano showers ash on Sicily? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "illness", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "fermentation", 
      "mammals", 
      "the effect of light on chemicals", 
      "nerves", 
      "mountains and their mapping", 
      "weather"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Pathology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kawaguchi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Hatogaya' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chevy Chase", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "Tom Hanks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1865", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1851", 
      "1832", 
      "1801"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Did The American Civil War End?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pre-Raphaelite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neo-Raphaelite", 
      "Pre-Jacobian", 
      "Neo-Jacobian"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of English painters formed in 1848. These artists attempted to recapture an old style of painting. They rejected industrialized England and focused on painting from nature, producing detailed, colorful works. What were they called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wind", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Solar", 
      "Tidal", 
      "Nuclear"
    ], 
    "question": "What energy does an Eolic power station generate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formula One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Cricket", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "Monza & Silverstone Are Venues For Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sean Penn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Jim Carrey"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Two and a Half Men and Milk feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Richard Donner", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Superman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Grenada is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lesotho", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Zambia", 
      "Angola", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Equatorial Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders South Africa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Full Dark, No Stars' was written by which American author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The War of the Worlds", 
      "Northern Lights", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "I Am Legend", 
      "The Amber Spyglass"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1979, which piece of written work starts with the line 'Far out in the uncharted backwaters of the unfashionable end of the western spiral arm of the Galaxy lies a small, unregarded yellow sun.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Severn\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Thames", 
      "The Trent", 
      "The Wye"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Is The Longest River In Britain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "bacteria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "a discipline that attempts to reconstruct the transmission of a text on the basis of relations between the various surviving manuscripts", 
      "Mars", 
      "the ancient Egyptians", 
      "the ecology of plant communities"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bacteriology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lappeenranta", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Yl\u00e4maa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Midnight Cowboy", 
      "Raging Bull"
    ], 
    "question": "The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Jones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Jackson", 
      "John Jones", 
      "Jim Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Twelfth Night", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "The Winter's Tale", 
      "Coriolanus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Shakespearean play refers to the date of epiphany?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ants", 
      "Grasshopper", 
      "Praying Mantis"
    ], 
    "question": "What insect has a type of hair on its eyes?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formula One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Cricket", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "Monza & Silverstone Are Venues For Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Julia Roberts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Natalie Portman", 
      "Nicole Kidman", 
      "Cate Blanchett", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Kirsten Dunst"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Ocean's Eleven and Pretty Woman feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Burton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Batman Returns?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The Gambia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fiji", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nauru", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Kiribati", 
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Palau", 
      "East Timor", 
      "New Zealand", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Japan", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Vietnam"
    ], 
    "question": "Solomon Islands shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "H. G. Wells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Douglas Adams", 
      "Lee Child", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Philip Pullman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English writer wrote 'The Invisible Man'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nineteen Eighty-Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Man in the High Castle", 
      "Blindness", 
      "Brave New World", 
      "The Road", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "The City & the City"
    ], 
    "question": "'It was a bright cold day in April, and the clocks were striking thirteen.' This is the first line of which 1949 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blue\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yellow", 
      "Red", 
      "White"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Colour Of The Cross On The Finish Flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "the purported influences of celestial bodies on earthly affairs", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "character", 
      "blackberries", 
      "venereal diseases"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Horology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kagoshima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Higashisakurajima?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hugh Grant", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Liam Neeson", 
      "Alan Rickman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the role of the Prime Minister, in the 2003 Christmas film 'Love Actually''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Babylon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlantis", 
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Scythia"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the Hanging Gardens?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dr Zhivago", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lolita", 
      "The Brothers Karamazov", 
      "The Cherry Orchard"
    ], 
    "question": "For which novel was Boris Pasternak awarded the 1958 Nobel Prize, an award he declined?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Protactinium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Potassium", 
      "Lead", 
      "Palladium"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the Chemical Element Pa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "West Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Won The First Football World Cup? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jared Leto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peter Cushing", 
      "Kenneth Branagh", 
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Dolph Lundgren", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Stephen Fry", 
      "Michael Ironside", 
      "Rowan Atkinson", 
      "Philippe Noiret", 
      "Richard Burton"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Suicide Squad and Requiem for a Dream?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stanley Kubrick", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed 2001: A Space Odyssey?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Federated States of Micronesia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tajikistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders People's Republic of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edgar Allan Poe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Mario Puzo", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Henry James", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Washington Irving", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Jack Vance"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Annabel Lee'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Great Gatsby", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Two households, both alike in dignity, in fair Verona, where we lay our scene, from ancient grudge break to new mutiny, where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Canada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "United States of America", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Cuba", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Honduras"
    ], 
    "question": "__________ is home to the world's most remote weather station. Its Eureka weather station is 600 miles from the North Pole.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "ancient multicelled plants", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "eggs", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections", 
      "viruses", 
      "angels", 
      "rheumatic diseases, a branch of medicine", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
      "reptiles and amphibians", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Paleophytology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Higashi\u014dsaka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Hiraoka?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pennsylvania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ohio", 
      "Maryland", 
      "Delaware"
    ], 
    "question": "In which American state is George A. Romero's 1968 film 'Night Of The Living Dead' set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1982", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1971", 
      "1964"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Macbeth", 
      "Juliette", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Shakespearean Character has the most lines in a single play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cp", 
      "Cm", 
      "Co"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the symbol for copper?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belgium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Italy", 
      "Austria"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1920 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert De Niro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Samuel L. Jackson", 
      "Bruce Willis", 
      "Liam Neeson", 
      "William Shatner", 
      "Christopher Lee", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Sean Connery"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Sesame Street and The Godfather trilogy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Eswatini is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Somalia", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Oman"
    ], 
    "question": "Seychelles shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prosper M\u00e9rim\u00e9e", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Maurice Leblanc", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Alexandre Dumas", 
      "Marcel Proust", 
      "Victor Hugo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which French writer, historian, and translator (1803-1870) wrote 'Carmen'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oahu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kauai", 
      "Hawaii", 
      "Maui"
    ], 
    "question": "On what island is Pearl Harbour?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "origin of life", 
      "earthquakes", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "study of devil worshipers", 
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms", 
      "algae", 
      "enzymes", 
      "music"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Helioseismology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lyon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Lugdunum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rembrandt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vermeer", 
      "Van Gogh", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hertz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Pascal", 
      "Newton", 
      "Ohm", 
      "Byte", 
      "Kelvin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the SI unit for frequency?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "8", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "5", 
      "14", 
      "20"
    ], 
    "question": "How many fighters are playable in 'Street Fighter II'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Burt Reynolds", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole", 
      "Richard Burton", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Tim Curry", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Stephen Fry", 
      "Kenneth Branagh"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The X-Files and Gunsmoke feature which American actor, director and producer of film and television (1936-2018)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Pulp Fiction?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Comoros is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kuwait", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Georgia", 
      "Syria", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Israel"
    ], 
    "question": "Iran shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Skeleton Crew' was written by which American author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lolita", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Ulysses", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Jin Ping Mei", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Slaughterhouse-Five", 
      "Justine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gambia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Namibia"
    ], 
    "question": "Banjul is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "minerals", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals that may or may not be mythical", 
      "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "the therapeutic use of plants", 
      "animal diseases", 
      "Mars", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context", 
      "the study or exploration of caves"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mineralogy the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hobart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sydney", 
      "Melbourne", 
      "Brisbane", 
      "Adelaide", 
      "Canberra", 
      "Perth", 
      "Geelong", 
      "Newcastle", 
      "Launceston", 
      "Ballarat"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Settlement of Sullivans Cove?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hiroshima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "Osaka", 
      "Nagasaki"
    ], 
    "question": "On What Japanese City Was The First Atomic Bomb Dropped?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Hardy", 
      "James Joyce", 
      "Emily Bront\u00eb", 
      "George Elliot"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"A Christmas Carol\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Red", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Purple", 
      "Yellow", 
      "Blue"
    ], 
    "question": "Which colour has highest wavelength in the visible spectrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mila Kunis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jacqueline Bisset", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Carey Mulligan", 
      "Rani Mukherjee", 
      "Audrey Hepburn"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Two and a Half Men and Black Swan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Lean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Lawrence of Arabia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Lesotho is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ireland", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Belgium", 
      "France", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Spain", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Austria", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "San Marino"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Danish Realm?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joseph Heller", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vladimir Nabokov", 
      "Kurt Vonnegut", 
      "Cassandra Clare", 
      "John Green", 
      "Mark Twain", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "James Fenimore Cooper", 
      "Jack London"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American author wrote 'Catch-22'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kidnapped", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Gargantua and Pantagruel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'You don\u2019t know about me without you have read a book by the name of The Adventures of Tom Sawyer; but that ain't no matter. That book was made by Mr. Mark Twain, and he told the truth, mainly. There were things which he stretched, but mainly he told the truth. That is nothing. I never seen anybody but lied one time or another, without it was Aunt Polly, or the widow, or maybe Mary.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Capital Of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure, development, and abnormalities of the teeth", 
      "vocal sounds", 
      "feces", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "study of horses", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "grasshoppers and crickets", 
      "butterflies and moths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Homology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "T\u00f8nsberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oslo", 
      "Bergen", 
      "Trondheim", 
      "Kongsvinger", 
      "Narvik"
    ], 
    "question": "'Sem' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nikita Khrushchev ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin", 
      "Vlademir Putin", 
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who gave John F. Kennedy a dog named Pushinka? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aesop", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Homer", 
      "Plato", 
      "Odysseus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Ancient Greek writer was famous for his Fables?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Insulin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estrogen", 
      "Keratin", 
      "Adrenaline"
    ], 
    "question": "What Hormone Controls The Supply Of Sugar From The Blood To The Muscles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Billy Bob Thornton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Colin Firth"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor, filmmaker, singer, songwriter, and musician has starred in films including Fargo and Armageddon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of The Godfather Part II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of The Gambia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mexico", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "United States of America", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Peru", 
      "Grenada"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guatemala?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Asimov", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Frank Herbert", 
      "William Gibson", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "Robert Silverberg"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Robots of Dawn' was written by which American writer and professor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frankenstein", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cloud Atlas", 
      "Coraline", 
      "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Gulliver's Travels", 
      "Flowers for Algernon", 
      "World War Z"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'You will rejoice to hear that no disaster has accompanied the commencement of an enterprise which you have regarded with such evil forebodings.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tripoli", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Benghazi", 
      "Tehran", 
      "Rabat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Libya? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "plankton", 
      "primates", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "human growth", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "myths", 
      "microorganisms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Genealogy the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Loimaa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Mellil\u00e4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Friday the 13th", 
      "Scream", 
      "IT"
    ], 
    "question": "Which series of films features a habitual serial killer called Michael Myers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Ruby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark Bench", 
      "Tom Gunn", 
      "Alvin Grey"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Shot Lee Harvey Oswald, The Assassin Of John F Kennedy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lithography", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Embography", 
      "Calligraphy", 
      "Recography"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the art of tracing designs and making impressions of them called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eyes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stinger", 
      "Wings", 
      "Lungs"
    ], 
    "question": "Honey Bees have hair on their ________. ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "15", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "21", 
      "25", 
      "20"
    ], 
    "question": "How many points win a game in badminton?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Clooney", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include ER and Tomorrowland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Schindler's List?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of The Gambia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nicaragua", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Belize", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Haiti", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Peru", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"
    ], 
    "question": "Costa Rica shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Johannes V. Jensen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hans Christian Andersen", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "James Joyce", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Fall of the King' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sense and Sensibility", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Candide", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Manon Lescaut", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'The family of Dashwood had been long settled in Sussex.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Denver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "classification", 
      "victims of crime, often applied to characterizing the criminal", 
      "the climate", 
      "symptoms", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "the historical study of languages", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Epistemology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Takamatsu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Sagita?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "It's a Wonderful Life", 
      "White Christmas"
    ], 
    "question": "From which film do we get the song 'White Christmas''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "John F Kennedy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "Malcolm X", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Virgil Grissom ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yuri Gagarin", 
      "Alan Shepard", 
      "Neil Armstrong"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the first man to go to space twice?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steffi Graff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billie Jean King", 
      "Venus Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rachel Weisz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include The Favourite and The Mummy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Lumet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed 12 Angry Men?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Suriname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thailand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Laos", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Palau", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "India", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Nepal", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Papua New Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Malaysia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hans Christian Andersen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beatrix Potter", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Astrid Lindgren", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Johannes V. Jensen", 
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Agatha Christie"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Little Mermaid' was written by which Danish author, fairy tale writer, and poet?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlotte's Web", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The City & the City", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "'In a hole in the ground there lived a hobbit.' This is the first line of which 1937 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ural", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pyrenees", 
      "Alps", 
      "Carpathian"
    ], 
    "question": "What mountain range separates Europe from Asia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the internal structures of stars as revealed by their oscillations", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "plants; botany", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "glaciers", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Asteroseismology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kagoshima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Higashisakurajima?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Baby Ruth candy bar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Smores", 
      "A Twinky", 
      "A Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the person chained to wall in Goonies want?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Canada"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1893, which country was the first to give women the vote?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Water Babies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oliver Twist", 
      "The Little Prince", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous book contains the line \"Once upon a time there was a little chimney sweep and his name was Tom\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alchemy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magic", 
      "Aurentalism", 
      "Mystic Metallurgy"
    ], 
    "question": "The ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steffi Graff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billie Jean King", 
      "Venus Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Meryl Streep", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cate Blanchett", 
      "Nicole Kidman", 
      "Natalie Portman", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Deer Hunter and Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Kiribati is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iraq", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Georgia", 
      "Syria", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Israel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Iran?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Darwin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
      "H. Rider Haggard", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Charles Dickens"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Descent of Man And Selection in Relation to Sex' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tibet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "feces", 
      "sleep", 
      "dragonflies and damselflies", 
      "the internal structures of stars as revealed by their oscillations", 
      "friction at very small scale", 
      "heat", 
      "origin of life", 
      "vaccines"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Tibetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nanjing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin", 
      "Wuhan"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nanking' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Friday the 13th", 
      "Scream", 
      "IT"
    ], 
    "question": "Which series of films features a habitual serial killer called Michael Myers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aesop", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Homer", 
      "Plato", 
      "Odysseus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Ancient Greek writer was famous for his Fables?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stainless Steel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aluminium", 
      "Einsteinium", 
      "Cast Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which metal was invented by British metallurgist Harold Brearley in 1912?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Foreman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joe Frazier", 
      "Wilfredo Gomez", 
      "Roberto Duran"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did Muhammed Ali Fight In 'The Rumble In The Jungle''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Curry", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aaron Paul", 
      "Mark Hamill", 
      "Richard Burton", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Joaquin Phoenix", 
      "Eric Roberts", 
      "Mickey Rooney", 
      "Burt Reynolds", 
      "Michael Ironside", 
      "Robert Mitchum"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Charlie's Angels and The Hunt for Red October feature which English actor, comedian and singer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Home Alone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Kiribati is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Azerbaijan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cyprus", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Romania", 
      "Egypt", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Albania", 
      "Belarus"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkey shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "G. K. Chesterton"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Murder of Roger Ackroyd'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.' This is the first line of which 1871 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Burma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Meenmar"
    ], 
    "question": "Myanmar was known as _____________ until 1989.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the effects of climate on living organisms", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "friction and lubrication", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "dreams", 
      "the writings and practices of historians", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the same as otolaryngology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bioclimatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Montreuil", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Charonne?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crete", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Babylon", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Bleak House", 
      "Wuthering Heights"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Mr Bennet' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lactic acid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Amenic Acid", 
      "Stomach Acid", 
      "Pectic Acid"
    ], 
    "question": "What chemical compound causes pain in muscles after exercise?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southpaw", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goofy", 
      "Regular", 
      "Orthodox"
    ], 
    "question": "What Do You Call A Boxer Who Leads With Their Right? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Richard Harris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sam Shepard", 
      "James Hong", 
      "Jon Bernthal", 
      "Gary Cooper", 
      "Terry Crews", 
      "Kevin Bacon", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Bill Hader", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone and Unforgiven feature which Irish actor, singer, film director and writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Batman Begins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Lesotho?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Burundi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Comoros", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "Angola", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Republic of the Congo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Tanzania?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "G. K. Chesterton"
    ], 
    "question": "'Partners in Crime' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "'There was Eru, the One, who in Arda is called Il\u00favatar; and he made first the Ainur, the Holy Ones, that were the offspring of his thought, and they were with him before aught else was made.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Capital Of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "venereal diseases", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "vocal sounds", 
      "grasshoppers and crickets", 
      "ants", 
      "children's behavior and development", 
      "minerals", 
      "periodic biological phenomena such as flowering, migration, breeding, etc", 
      "Mars", 
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Venereology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Akashi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'\u014ckubo' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spilled champagne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A lightning strike", 
      "Divine intervention", 
      "A plutonium power core"
    ], 
    "question": "What caused the computer in Electric Dreams to become alive?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aqueduct", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canal", 
      "Forum", 
      "Arena"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the Romans build to convey water? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Water Babies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oliver Twist", 
      "The Little Prince", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous book contains the line \"Once upon a time there was a little chimney sweep and his name was Tom\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Liver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kidney", 
      "Stomach", 
      "Bladder"
    ], 
    "question": "What does hepatitis affect?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "UEFA Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Intertoto Cup", 
      "Europa Cup", 
      "UEFA Champions' League"
    ], 
    "question": "What Did The Inter Cities Fairs Cup Change It's Name To?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Laura Dern", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Sally Hawkins"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actress, director, producer has starred in films including Twin Peaks and Star Wars: Episode VIII \u2013 The Last Jedi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert Zemeckis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Forrest Gump?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Bahrain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Monaco", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Poland", 
      "Slovakia"
    ], 
    "question": "Switzerland shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jack Vance", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "William Gibson"
    ], 
    "question": "'Barsoom' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "Sancho Panza appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jane Eyre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "Little Women", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The Red and the Black"
    ], 
    "question": "'There was no possibility of taking a walk that day.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Monaco", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Italy", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "France", 
      "Belgium"
    ], 
    "question": "_________ sits on the southern coast of France, near the border with Italy, and covers 0.73 square miles (approximately 1/2 the size of New York's Central Park).", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "trees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "crayfish", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the anatomy of blood and lymph vascular systems", 
      "Jack the Ripper and the crimes associated with him", 
      "friction and lubrication"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dendrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kaarina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Piikki\u00f6?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dog", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horse", 
      "Goat", 
      "Ghost"
    ], 
    "question": "The only __________ to ever appear in a Shakespearean play was Crab in \"The Two Gentlemen of Verona.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Trampling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eating", 
      "Drowning", 
      "Mauling"
    ], 
    "question": "Hippopotamuses have killed more people in Africa than all the lions, elephants, and water buffalo combined, usually by __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nurburgring", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hokkenheim", 
      "Spa", 
      "Monza"
    ], 
    "question": "Which German Grand Prix circuit was used for a Formula 1 race for the last time in 1976, when Niki Lauda was almost killed?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sarah Paulson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Sally Hawkins"
    ], 
    "question": "The films American Horror Story and 12 Years a Slave feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Lucas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Star Wars?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colombia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El Salvador", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Panama", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Haiti", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Nicaragua?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Johannes V. Jensen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hans Christian Andersen", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "James Joyce", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Digte' was written by which Danish author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ulysses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "Lolita", 
      "The Brothers Karamazov", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias"
    ], 
    "question": "'Stately, plump Buck Mulligan came from the stairhead, bearing a bowl of lather on which a mirror and a razor lay crossed.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Bronx", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manhattan", 
      "Harlem", 
      "Brooklyn"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the only borough of New York City that is not on an island? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "windmills, watermills and animal engines", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract", 
      "study of horses", 
      "Japanese people", 
      "fossils of ancient life", 
      "venereal diseases"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Molinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Varkaus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Kangaslampi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Babylon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlantis", 
      "Jerusalem", 
      "Scythia"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the Hanging Gardens?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Pratchett", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Brandon Sanderson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author penned the Discworld Series of sci-fi novels?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Crash", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Loom", 
      "A Brush", 
      "A Forest"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Collective Name For Rhinoceroses?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "UEFA Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Intertoto Cup", 
      "Europa Cup", 
      "UEFA Champions' League"
    ], 
    "question": "What Did The Inter Cities Fairs Cup Change It's Name To?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christian Bale", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Brian Cox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Dark Knight and American Hustle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Cameron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Titanic?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "San Marino is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Singapore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Japan", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "Indonesia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "G. K. Chesterton"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Poirot Investigates'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", 
      "Robinson Crusoe"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mississippi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arkansas", 
      "Alabama", 
      "Louisiana"
    ], 
    "question": "In which state is the Natchez Trail?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Shroud of Turin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the functions of the nervous system", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "statistics such as births, deaths, income, or the incidence of disease, which illustrate the changing structure of human populations", 
      "the future", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "neural diseases", 
      "clouds", 
      "old age"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Sindonology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kakogawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shikata?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spilled champagne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A lightning strike", 
      "Divine intervention", 
      "A plutonium power core"
    ], 
    "question": "What caused the computer in Electric Dreams to become alive?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Black Prince", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The White Prince", 
      "The Red Prince", 
      "The Green Prince"
    ], 
    "question": "What was The Eldest Son Of Edward III Better Known As?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joanne Kathleen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Julia Kathleen", 
      "Joanne Katherine", 
      "Julia Katherine"
    ], 
    "question": "What do the initials \"JK\" stand for in the name \"JK Rowling\", Author of the \"Harry Potter\" books?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Universe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Milky Way", 
      "Andromeda", 
      "Infinity"
    ], 
    "question": "What was created with the big bang?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Orioles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ravens", 
      "Yankees", 
      "Jays"
    ], 
    "question": "Baseball: The Baltimore ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Rani Mukherjee", 
      "Liv Ullmann", 
      "Margot Robbie", 
      "Claudia Cardinale", 
      "Marlene Dietrich"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Die Another Day and Dick Tracy feature which American singer and songwriter?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yemen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eritrea", 
      "Israel", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Iran", 
      "Syria", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Sudan", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Azerbaijan"
    ], 
    "question": "Saudi Arabia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British novelist wrote 'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "On the Origin of Species", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Germinal", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "'When we look to the individuals of the same variety or sub\u2010variety of our older cultivated plants and animals, one of the first points which strikes us, is, that they generally differ much more from each other, than do the individuals of any one species or variety in a state of nature.' This is the first line of which 1859 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Manila\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jakarta", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Bandung"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Is The Capital Of The Philippines?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the fetus, especially when within the uterus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the future", 
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "crime", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study, especially statistical, of elections", 
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Fetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Vehkalahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Declaration Of Independence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Constitution", 
      "The Emancipation Procalation", 
      "The Liberty Decree"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 1776 American Affirmation Asserted The Basic Rights Of All?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "Anna Karenina"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Mr. Darcy' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Protactinium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Potassium", 
      "Lead", 
      "Palladium"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the Chemical Element Pa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robotic Operating Buddy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Random Object Builder", 
      "Realistic Orbital Belt", 
      "Routed Oval Beam"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the letters in ROB (the old NES peripheral) stand for?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Denis O'Hare", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Jim Carrey"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor has starred in films including American Horror Story and True Blood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Cameron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Aliens?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Antigua and Barbuda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Senegal", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Niger", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Ivory Coast?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mario Puzo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "L. Frank Baum", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "John Green", 
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Herman Melville", 
      "Frank Herbert"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American writer wrote 'The Godfather'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lolita", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Ulysses", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Jin Ping Mei", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Slaughterhouse-Five", 
      "Justine"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1955, which piece of written work starts with the line 'Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Bay Of Pigs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "music in society, usually non-western music", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "friction and lubrication", 
      "oceans", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "blackberries", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ethnomusicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fukushima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Sasaya?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jingle All The Way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Santa Clause", 
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "Bad Santa"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Popular Christmas Movie Featured A Must Have Toy Called 'Turbo Man''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1982", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1971", 
      "1964"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Foreshortening", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Isometric Projection", 
      "Topomorphism", 
      "Skewed Perspective"
    ], 
    "question": "Which art technique can be described as \"Reducing or distorting in order to represent three-dimensional space as perceived by the eye\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Computer Mouse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Electric Watch", 
      "Fingerprint scanner", 
      "Microwave"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Gadget Was Invented By Douglas Englebart In 1964", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baby Pac-Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miss Pac-Man", 
      "Mrs Pac-Man", 
      "Super Pac-Man"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frances Fisher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The X-Files and Castle feature which English-born American actress?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Lucas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Star Wars: Episode II \u2013 Attack of the Clones?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Belize is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sierra Leone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Togo", 
      "Mali", 
      "Benin", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Niger", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Liberia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dante Alighieri", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Giovanni Boccaccio", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Francisco Quevedo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Italian poet wrote 'Inferno'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", 
      "Robinson Crusoe"
    ], 
    "question": "'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pacific Ocean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Indian Ocean", 
      "Atlantic Ocean", 
      "Mediterranean Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "The Philippines is an archipelago of 7,107 islands in the ________________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the relationship between electric phenomena and bodily processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "ligaments", 
      "the future", 
      "demons", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "illness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Electrophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "Lucerne", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Lugano", 
      "Fribourg"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Bramois?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "Scream", 
      "Child's Play"
    ], 
    "question": "The Character Of Mike Myers Features Heavily In Which Series Of Horror Movies?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Genghis Khan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timur", 
      "Augustus", 
      "Xerxes"
    ], 
    "question": "What did Temujin change his name to?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dog", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horse", 
      "Goat", 
      "Ghost"
    ], 
    "question": "The only __________ to ever appear in a Shakespearean play was Crab in \"The Two Gentlemen of Verona.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Giraffes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rhinos", 
      "Deer", 
      "Elk"
    ], 
    "question": "__________ are the only animals born with horns.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Table Tennis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pool", 
      "Volleyball", 
      "Wrestling"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Sport Was Desmond Douglas Britain's Leading Competitor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bradley Cooper", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Russell Crowe"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Guardians of the Galaxy and Alias feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ridley Scott", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Blade Runner?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Palau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Gabon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Zambia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets' was written by which British novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The War of the Worlds", 
      "Northern Lights", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "I Am Legend", 
      "The Amber Spyglass"
    ], 
    "question": "'Far out in the uncharted backwaters of the unfashionable end of the western spiral arm of the Galaxy lies a small, unregarded yellow sun.' This is the first line of which 1979 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria and Italy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estonia and Latvia", 
      "Iran and Iraq", 
      "Morocco and Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "What two countries do Tyroleans come from? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "waves or wave motions", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "weather", 
      "Tibet", 
      "mental processes in living creatures", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "dietetics", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract", 
      "the age of the Earth"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Kymatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kajaani", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Vuolijoki' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "I Love Lucy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Brady Bunch", 
      "Sanford and Son", 
      "My Favourite Martian"
    ], 
    "question": "What popular US TV sitcom With 3 Words made its first appearance in 1951 & ran until 1957?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Withers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Jackson", 
      "Luther Vandross", 
      "Marvin Gaye"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had An 80's Hit With The Song 'Just The Two of Us,'? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Twelfth Night", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "The Winter's Tale", 
      "Coriolanus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Shakespearean play refers to the date of epiphany?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nose", 
      "Hand", 
      "Foot"
    ], 
    "question": "Where in the body is the smallest human muscle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mayfair", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kensington", 
      "Trafalgar Square", 
      "Old Kent Road"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Most Valuble Property In A Game Of British Monopoly?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ken Jeong", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "John Turturro"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Community and Avengers: Endgame feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Lucas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Star Wars: Episode II \u2013 Attack of the Clones?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Seychelles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cambodia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vietnam", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "India", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Palau"
    ], 
    "question": "Thailand shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jude Watson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Brandon Sanderson", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Herman Melville", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs"
    ], 
    "question": "'The 39 Clues' was written by which American novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The City & the City", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mr Utterson the lawyer was a man of a rugged countenance, that was never lighted by a smile; cold, scanty and embarrassed in discourse; backward in sentiment; lean, long, dusty, dreary and yet somehow lovable.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venezuela", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canada", 
      "Scotland", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ possesses more proven oil reserves than any country outside the Middle East.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "wood", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "mountains and their mapping", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "men", 
      "eggs", 
      "interactions among organisms and the water cycle"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Xylology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kitee", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Kes\u00e4lahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Midnight Cowboy", 
      "Raging Bull"
    ], 
    "question": "The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dwight Eisenhower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin Roosevelt", 
      "Lyndon Johnson", 
      "Jimmy Carter"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was President of the USA from 1953 till 1961?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Water Babies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oliver Twist", 
      "The Little Prince", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous book contains the line \"Once upon a time there was a little chimney sweep and his name was Tom\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sciatic nerve", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Optic nerve", 
      "Lumbar plexus", 
      "Ulnar nerve"
    ], 
    "question": "Which is the largest nerve in the Human Body?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "UEFA Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Intertoto Cup", 
      "Europa Cup", 
      "UEFA Champions' League"
    ], 
    "question": "What Did The Inter Cities Fairs Cup Change It's Name To?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jason Bateman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Russell Crowe"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Arrested Development and Up in the Air feature which American actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of X2?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Antigua and Barbuda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ireland", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Belgium", 
      "France", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Spain", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Austria", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "San Marino"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Danish Realm?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English writer and social critic wrote 'A Christmas Carol'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Study in Scarlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "The Shadow of the Wind", 
      "Inferno", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Angels & Demons", 
      "The Da Vinci Code", 
      "The Lost Symbol", 
      "The Caves of Steel"
    ], 
    "question": "'In the year 1878 I took my degree of Doctor of Medicine of the University of London, and proceeded to Netley to go through the course prescribed for surgeons in the army.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Reykjavik", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ontario", 
      "Moscow", 
      "Helsinki"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The World's Most Northerly Capital City?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "lightning", 
      "measurement", 
      "the classical Chinese literary masterpiece Dream of the Red Chamber", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "wine", 
      "flies", 
      "bones", 
      "sacred texts"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cryology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sopron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Budapest", 
      "Debrecen", 
      "Szeged", 
      "P\u00e9cs", 
      "Miskolc", 
      "Gy\u0151r", 
      "Sz\u00e9kesfeh\u00e9rv\u00e1r", 
      "Szombathely", 
      "Kecskem\u00e9t", 
      "Eger"
    ], 
    "question": "'Scarbantia' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oklahoma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Missouri", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ray Bradbury", 
      "Joseph Heller", 
      "Harper Lee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"The Great Gatsby\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Urinate", 
      "Bark", 
      "Mate"
    ], 
    "question": "A skunk will not __________ and throw its scent at the same time.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baseball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Basketball", 
      "Football", 
      "Ice Hockey"
    ], 
    "question": "Which sport is played by the Minnesota Twins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Forest Whitaker", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Donald Sutherland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor has starred in films including Criminal Minds and Black Panther?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed X-Men: Days of Future Past?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Maldives?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Niger", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinea", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Morocco"
    ], 
    "question": "Burkina Faso shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "H. G. Wells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Douglas Adams", 
      "Lee Child", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Philip Pullman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English writer wrote 'The Invisible Man'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlotte's Web", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The City & the City", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1937, which piece of written work starts with the line 'In a hole in the ground there lived a hobbit.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mojave", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sonoran", 
      "Arizonan", 
      "Baja"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the desert located in South East California.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the art and career of using cosmetics to improve beauty", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "the Sumerians", 
      "proper names", 
      "existence", 
      "communist Soviet Union", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "cells"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cosmetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kaarina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Piikki\u00f6' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jason", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie", 
      "Mike", 
      "Chuckie"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Bad Guy In The Friday The 13th Series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "King Lear", 
      "Julius Caesar", 
      "Othello", 
      "Coriolanus", 
      "Anthony and Cleopatra"
    ], 
    "question": "In which Shakespearean tragedy Does Laertes appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hertz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Pascal", 
      "Newton", 
      "Ohm", 
      "Byte", 
      "Kelvin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the SI unit for frequency?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Houston", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Settle", 
      "Miami"
    ], 
    "question": "The Rockets Basketball Team & The Astros Baseball Team Both Hail From Which US City?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charlize Theron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Keira Knightley"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Mad Max: Fury Road and Prometheus?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Antigua and Barbuda is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "United Kingdom", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barbados", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Panama", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Cuba"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Venezuela?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "E. B. White", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Cassandra Clare", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Henry James", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Donna Leon", 
      "Robert Silverberg"
    ], 
    "question": "'Charlotte's Web' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The A.B.C. Murders", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "Lolita", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "American Psycho (book)", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Crime and Punishment"
    ], 
    "question": "'It was in June of 1935 that I came home from my ranch in South America for a stay of about six months.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mont Blanc\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mount Etna", 
      "Elbrus", 
      "Grossglockner"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Highest Mountain In The Alps?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study and interpretation of symbols, or a set of symbols", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the structure of cells", 
      "the process of biological evolution", 
      "reptiles and amphibians", 
      "minerals", 
      "grasshoppers and crickets", 
      "feces", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "grasses"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Symbology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pargas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio", 
      "Porvoo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Pargas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rudyard Kipling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A A Milne", 
      "Roald Dahl", 
      "C S Lewis"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote the \"Just So Stories\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hydroponics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horticulture", 
      "Apedology", 
      "Anapedics"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Method Of Growing Plants Without Soil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ipswich Town", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plymouth Argyle", 
      "Norwich City", 
      "Bristol Rovers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English football team are nicknamed the Tractor Boys?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Billy Bob Thornton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Colin Firth"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Fargo and Armageddon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Cameron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Terminator 2: Judgment Day?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Federated States of Micronesia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malawi", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Mauritius", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Djibouti"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Comoros?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "William Shakespeare", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "Isaac Newton", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Lee Child", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "J. K. Rowling"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Tempest' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuor appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Women", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Candide", 
      "The Neverending Story"
    ], 
    "question": "''Christmas won't be Christmas without any presents'' This is the first line of which 1868 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Poland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Slovakia", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Lake Ladoga Is The Largest Lake In Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "vocal sounds", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "shells and of molluscs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Edaphology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sint-Truiden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brussels", 
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Brussels-Capital Region", 
      "Anderlecht"
    ], 
    "question": "'Gelmen' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Midnight Cowboy", 
      "Raging Bull"
    ], 
    "question": "The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Italy", 
      "China", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country blew up a Greenpeace ship in New Zealand?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Christmas Carol", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Hound of the Baskervilles", 
      "Poirot", 
      "Fahrenheit 451"
    ], 
    "question": "Which famous book begins with the line \"Marley was dead, to begin with. There was no doubt about that\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Milky way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andromedu", 
      "Ursa", 
      "Orion"
    ], 
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known called _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Middlesex", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Essex", 
      "Surrey", 
      "Berkshire"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which County Is Lord's Cricket Ground?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michelle Williams", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Brokeback Mountain and Venom?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iran", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cyprus", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Romania", 
      "Egypt", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Albania", 
      "Belarus"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkey shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Umberto Eco", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Orhan Pamuk", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Jos\u00e9 Saramago", 
      "Paulo Coelho", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "'Norwegian Wood' was written by which Japanese writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Great Gatsby", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "'Two households, both alike in dignity, in fair Verona, where we lay our scene, from ancient grudge break to new mutiny, where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Algiers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oran", 
      "Constantine", 
      "Rabat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Algeria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "a set of words and/or phrases, usually in relation to some particular canon or field of study", 
      "China", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "the future", 
      "the eyes", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Micrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sapporo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Toyohira?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Friday the 13th", 
      "Scream", 
      "IT"
    ], 
    "question": "Which series of films features a habitual serial killer called Michael Myers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four Years", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One Year", 
      "Nine Years", 
      "Seven Years"
    ], 
    "question": "How Long Was The American Civil War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ray Bradbury", 
      "Joseph Heller", 
      "Harper Lee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"The Great Gatsby\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Feet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antennae", 
      "Nose", 
      "Anus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Does A Butterfly Use To Taste?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "England"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paul Newman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Roger Moore"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Sting and The Towering Inferno feature which American actor and film director (1925\u20132008)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Apocalypse Now?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pakistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "People's Republic of China shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Joyce", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Samuel Beckett", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Dubliners' was written by which Irish novelist and poet?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.' This is the first line of which 1999 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria and Italy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estonia and Latvia", 
      "Iran and Iraq", 
      "Morocco and Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "What two countries do Tyroleans come from? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "pollen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "musical instruments", 
      "drugs", 
      "study of refuse and trash", 
      "the Islam", 
      "the Assyrians", 
      "diseases of stomach and intestines", 
      "Jack the Ripper and the crimes associated with him", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Palynology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kauhava", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Ylih\u00e4rm\u00e4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Louis XVI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Louis XIII", 
      "Charles VIII", 
      "Charles XI"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Marie Antoinette's Husband?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "King Lear", 
      "Julius Caesar", 
      "Othello", 
      "Coriolanus", 
      "Anthony and Cleopatra"
    ], 
    "question": "In which Shakespearean tragedy Does Laertes appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Es", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El", 
      "En", 
      "Ei"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for einsteinium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "16", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12", 
      "10", 
      "14"
    ], 
    "question": "How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frances Conroy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Charlize Theron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Joker and Scent of a Woman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Lean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Lawrence of Arabia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Antigua and Barbuda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Monaco", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Poland", 
      "Slovakia"
    ], 
    "question": "Switzerland shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Darwin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
      "H. Rider Haggard", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Charles Dickens"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Origin of Species' was written by which British naturalist, author of \"On the origin of species, by means of natural selection\" (1809-1882)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Mockingjay", 
      "Eclipse"
    ], 
    "question": "'Mr and Mrs Dursley, of number four, Privet Drive, were proud to say that they were perfectly normal, thank you very much.' This is the first line of which 1997 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Bay Of Pigs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the nature of values and value judgements", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "existence", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "neural diseases", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "the study or skill of preparing mixed drinks", 
      "the larynx, or voice box; a branch of medicine", 
      "the structure, function, and pathology of the ear", 
      "wine and winemaking"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Axiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sopron", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Budapest", 
      "Debrecen", 
      "Szeged", 
      "P\u00e9cs", 
      "Miskolc", 
      "Gy\u0151r", 
      "Sz\u00e9kesfeh\u00e9rv\u00e1r", 
      "Szombathely", 
      "Kecskem\u00e9t", 
      "Eger"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Scarbantia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Godiva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lady Gaga", 
      "Lady Geronimo", 
      "Lady Galebe"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is famous for historically riding naked on horseback through Coventry, England?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Twelfth Night", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "The Winter's Tale", 
      "Coriolanus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Shakespearean play refers to the date of epiphany?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nose", 
      "Hand", 
      "Foot"
    ], 
    "question": "Where in the body is the smallest human muscle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "UEFA Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Intertoto Cup", 
      "Europa Cup", 
      "UEFA Champions' League"
    ], 
    "question": "What Did The Inter Cities Fairs Cup Change It's Name To?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Faye Dunaway", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including CSI: Crime Scene Investigation and Bonnie and Clyde?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "William Wyler", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Ben-Hur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Central African Republic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Benin", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Chad", 
      "Togo", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Niger", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Burkina Faso"
    ], 
    "question": "Republic of the Congo shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Return of Sherlock Holmes'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Study in Scarlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "The Shadow of the Wind", 
      "Inferno", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Angels & Demons", 
      "The Da Vinci Code", 
      "The Lost Symbol", 
      "The Caves of Steel"
    ], 
    "question": "'In the year 1878 I took my degree of Doctor of Medicine of the University of London, and proceeded to Netley to go through the course prescribed for surgeons in the army.' This is the first line of which 1887 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Honolulu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hilo", 
      "Kailua", 
      "Maui"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Hawaii?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the relationship between electric phenomena and bodily processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "ligaments", 
      "the future", 
      "demons", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "illness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Electrophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "Lucerne", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Lugano", 
      "Fribourg"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Bramois?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Axel Foley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Johnny West", 
      "Marcus Steel", 
      "Jarvis Hansen"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the name of Eddie Murphy's character in Beverly Hills Cop?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Auckland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christchurch", 
      "Adelaide", 
      "Brisbane"
    ], 
    "question": "In the harbour of which city was the Greenpeace flagship Rainbow Warrior sunk in 1985?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michelangelo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leonardo", 
      "Raphael", 
      "Donatello"
    ], 
    "question": "By what name is the great italian sculptor & artist Buonarroti better known?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rd", 
      "Gi", 
      "Rm"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for radium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ralph Fiennes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Mark Wahlberg", 
      "Leonardo DiCaprio", 
      "John Travolta", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Josh Brolin", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Danny DeVito", 
      "Denis O'Hare", 
      "Adam Sandler"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire and Schindler's List?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Apocalypse Now?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Suriname is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "El Salvador", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Belize", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago"
    ], 
    "question": "Honduras shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Lightning Thief", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Not for the first time, an argument had broken out over breakfast at number four, Privet drive'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belgium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "France", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Germany", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Denmark"
    ], 
    "question": "Brussels is the capital of which country", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "birds", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "myths", 
      "the attribute (of a word) of being self descriptive", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "bees", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ornithology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matsudo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takagi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "Scream", 
      "Child's Play"
    ], 
    "question": "The Character Of Mike Myers Features Heavily In Which Series Of Horror Movies?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Submarine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Torpedo", 
      "TNT", 
      "The Tank"
    ], 
    "question": "Designed By Robert Fulton, Which Weapon Was Tested In The Seine In 1801?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boys", 
      "Witches", 
      "Game"
    ], 
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's _________\".", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "2", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "4", 
      "10"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Only Even Prime Number? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Orange", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue", 
      "Yellow", 
      "Red"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Grade Follows A Yellow Belt In Judo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hugo Weaving", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tobey Maguire", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Elijah Wood", 
      "Dennis Hopper", 
      "Jack Lemmon", 
      "Paul Newman", 
      "Bill Hader", 
      "Ken Jeong", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Gary Cooper"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English-Australian actor has starred in films including The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King and Captain America: The First Avenger?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "William Wyler", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Ben-Hur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Suriname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Algeria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Portugal", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Mali", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "France", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Malta", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Italy", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Niger"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Morocco?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fyodor Dostoyevsky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vladimir Nabokov", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Nikolai Gogol", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Mikhail Lermontov"
    ], 
    "question": "'Demons' was written by which Russian author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Two Towers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Last Battle"
    ], 
    "question": "'Aragorn sped on up the hill.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dominican Republic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Haiti", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "What country is Santo Domingo the capital of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "dragonflies and damselflies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wine", 
      "myths", 
      "race", 
      "the field of dermatological anatomical pathology", 
      "earthquakes", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "the functions of the nervous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Odonatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ibaraki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Ishikawa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frank Capra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orson Welles", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Howard Hawks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed the 1946 classic 'It's A Wonderful Life'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Britain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "France", 
      "Germany", 
      "China"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the third country to get the atomic bomb?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thomas Hardy", 
      "Emily Bronte", 
      "Jane Austen"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Great Expectations\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alchemy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magic", 
      "Aurentalism", 
      "Mystic Metallurgy"
    ], 
    "question": "The ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Surfing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Skate Boarding", 
      "Skiing", 
      "Boxing"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Hotdog & Bottom Trun\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Angela Bassett", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Madonna"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including American Horror Story and Black Panther?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of East Timor is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kazakhstan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders People's Republic of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edgar Allan Poe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Mario Puzo", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Henry James", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Washington Irving", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Jack Vance"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American author, poet, editor and literary critic wrote 'The Bells'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.' This is the first line of which 1871 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Budapest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "P\u00e9cs", 
      "Prague", 
      "Salzburg", 
      "Bratislava"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Hungary? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the Soviet Union", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the study and design of machines at the molecular level", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "schematic layouts"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Kremlinology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hirakata", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Kawagoshi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tracy Ullman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vanessa Phillips", 
      "Paula Skeeberg", 
      "Mary Myers"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the female comedy star who once had a show on Fox, that had a pop hit in the early eighties", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Pratchett", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Brandon Sanderson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author penned the Discworld Series of sci-fi novels?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Octopus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pelican", 
      "Squid", 
      "Albatross"
    ], 
    "question": "A giant Pacific __________ can fit its entire body through an opening no bigger than the size of its beak.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jack", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Nightmare", 
      "The Flush", 
      "The Drone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The White Ball In A Game Of Bowls?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jennifer Aniston", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Maggie Smith"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Friends and The Iron Giant feature which American actress, film producer and businesswoman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Peter Jackson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Palau is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "San Marino", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Albania", 
      "Germany", 
      "Poland", 
      "Monaco", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Romania", 
      "Malta"
    ], 
    "question": "Slovenia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jules Verne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Victor Hugo", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Margaret Atwood", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Maurice Leblanc", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Guy de Maupassant", 
      "Arthur C. Clarke"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'A Journey to the Center of the Earth'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Capital Of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the interrelationship between an organism's physical functioning and its environment", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "clouds", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "flow", 
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs", 
      "fungi"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ecophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Suita", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shinden?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "I Love Lucy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Brady Bunch", 
      "Sanford and Son", 
      "My Favourite Martian"
    ], 
    "question": "What popular US TV sitcom With 3 Words made its first appearance in 1951 & ran until 1957?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Germany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Denmark", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Van Gogh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salvador Dali", 
      "Andy Warhol", 
      "Raphael", 
      "Vermeer"
    ], 
    "question": "Which painter reputedly cut of his own ear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ostrich", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peacock", 
      "Emu", 
      "Emperor Penguin"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the largest living bird.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steffi Graff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billie Jean King", 
      "Venus Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Clint Eastwood", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Christopher Lee", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Good, the Bad and the Ugly and Million Dollar Baby feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed The Godfather Part II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Mauritius?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "United States of America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Nauru", 
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Vanuatu", 
      "Fiji", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "Palau", 
      "New Zealand", 
      "Australia", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Japan", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Brunei", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Vietnam"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Kiribati?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nikolai Gogol", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Mikhail Lermontov", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Vladimir Nabokov", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Marquis de Sade", 
      "Samuel Beckett"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Overcoat'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Women", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Candide", 
      "The Neverending Story"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1868, which piece of written work starts with the line ''Christmas won't be Christmas without any presents''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mexico", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Argentina", 
      "Bolivia"
    ], 
    "question": "With which country is Fidel Castro associated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "minerals", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "disease classification", 
      "water", 
      "fresh water environments, particularly lakes", 
      "lightning", 
      "prehistoric people and human origins"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dendrochronology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "New York City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "Baltimore", 
      "Seattle", 
      "Indianapolis"
    ], 
    "question": "'New Amsterdam' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jingle All The Way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Santa Clause", 
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "Bad Santa"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Popular Christmas Movie Featured A Must Have Toy Called 'Turbo Man''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Walter Raleigh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sir Francis Drake", 
      "James Cook", 
      "Ernest Shackleton"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Brought Back Tobacco And Potatoes From The Americas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Othello", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "What shakespearean play features the line: \"A plague on both your houses\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Dial Telephone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Hearing Aid", 
      "The Telegram", 
      "The Microphone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Communication Aid Was Invented In 1905 By American Undertaker Almon Strowger", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oxford", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manchester", 
      "London", 
      "York", 
      "Southampton", 
      "Norwich"
    ], 
    "question": "In which English city did Roger Bannister become the first man to run a mile in under 4 minutes? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matt Damon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Lee", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Liam Neeson", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Christian Bale"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Thor: Ragnarok and Deadpool 2 feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Trinidad and Tobago is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Mali", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Niger", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Portugal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guinea-Bissau?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "H. Rider Haggard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Jin Yong", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English writer of adventure novels wrote 'King Solomon's Mines'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Study in Scarlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "The Shadow of the Wind", 
      "Inferno", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Angels & Demons", 
      "The Da Vinci Code", 
      "The Lost Symbol", 
      "The Caves of Steel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'In the year 1878 I took my degree of Doctor of Medicine of the University of London, and proceeded to Netley to go through the course prescribed for surgeons in the army.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belize", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guatemala", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest North?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or exploration of caves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "methods", 
      "methods", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "glaciers", 
      "cancer", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Speleology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kyoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called N\u014dso?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Midnight Cowboy", 
      "Raging Bull"
    ], 
    "question": "The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ming", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qin", 
      "Han", 
      "Tang"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard III", 
      "Henry VII", 
      "James IV"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1526 Hans Holbein became the official portrait painter of which english king?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Distance", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Time", 
      "Pressure", 
      "Magnetism"
    ], 
    "question": " What does a micron measure?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "8", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "5", 
      "14", 
      "20"
    ], 
    "question": "How many fighters are playable in 'Street Fighter II'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Patrick Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Pierce Brosnan"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Fargo and Prometheus feature which American actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of The Dark Knight?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Mauritius is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lithuania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poland", 
      "Finland", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Romania", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Austria", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Montenegro"
    ], 
    "question": "Latvia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guy de Maupassant", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Anatole France", 
      "Albert Camus", 
      "Octave Mirbeau", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Victor Hugo", 
      "Stendhal", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which French writer wrote 'Au soleil'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nineteen Eighty-Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Man in the High Castle", 
      "Blindness", 
      "Brave New World", 
      "The Road", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The Windup Girl", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "The City & the City"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'It was a bright cold day in April, and the clocks were striking thirteen.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Atlantic\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pacific", 
      "Indian", 
      "Arctic"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Ocean Is The Gulf Stream", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "writing systems", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the field of dermatological anatomical pathology", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "existence", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "the scientific study of baths, bathing and of their application to disease", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "demons", 
      "snakes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Grammatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokkaichi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Tomida' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "It's a Wonderful Life", 
      "White Christmas"
    ], 
    "question": "From which film do we get the song 'White Christmas''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Neville Chamberlain", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Winston Churchill", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Clement Atlee"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the British Prime Minister at the outbreak of the Second World War?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Hardy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Far From The Madding Crowd\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Larva", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bulba", 
      "Curla", 
      "Meta"
    ], 
    "question": "The four stages in the lifecycle of an insect are: egg, adult, pupa, and ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Beckham", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Owen", 
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "David Seaman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English Footballer Was Sent Off In The 1998 World Cup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dan Aykroyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Danny Glover", 
      "Danny Trejo", 
      "Dustin Hoffman", 
      "Harry Dean Stanton", 
      "Forest Whitaker", 
      "Charlton Heston", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Jack Nicholson", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Canadian film actor and comedian has starred in films including Saturday Night Live and Ghostbusters?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed X2?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of The Gambia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Afghanistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pakistan", 
      "Iran", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Oman", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "India", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Uzbekistan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Astrid Lindgren", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Hans Christian Andersen", 
      "Lucy Maud Montgomery", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Swedish writer of children's books, song lyrics and screenplays wrote 'The Brothers Lionheart'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Lightning Thief", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery"
    ], 
    "question": "'Not for the first time, an argument had broken out over breakfast at number four, Privet drive' This is the first line of which 1998 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colorado", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arizona", 
      "Utah", 
      "Florida"
    ], 
    "question": "The highest point in Pennsylvania is lower than the lowest point in ______________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "true bugs", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a synonym of Pulmonology", 
      "study of the mouth and its diseases", 
      "the Shroud of Turin", 
      "the scientific study of baths, bathing and of their application to disease", 
      "cats", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "the mathematical study of closeness and connectedness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Heteroptology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chigasaki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Tsurugamine' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Baby Ruth candy bar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Smores", 
      "A Twinky", 
      "A Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the person chained to wall in Goonies want?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hoover", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin", 
      "Roosevelt", 
      "Johnson"
    ], 
    "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pre-Raphaelite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neo-Raphaelite", 
      "Pre-Jacobian", 
      "Neo-Jacobian"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of English painters formed in 1848. These artists attempted to recapture an old style of painting. They rejected industrialized England and focused on painting from nature, producing detailed, colorful works. What were they called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pangaea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Laurasia", 
      "Rodinia", 
      "Gondwana"
    ], 
    "question": "What name is given to the single super-continent that existed 200 million years ago?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Driver Has Been Disqualified", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Race Has Been Won", 
      "A Driver Has Died", 
      "The Fastest Lap Has Been Set"
    ], 
    "question": "In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Stiller", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Ben Kingsley"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Sesame Street and DodgeBall: A True Underdog Story feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ridley Scott", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Alien?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Palau?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Algeria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cameroon", 
      "Togo", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Malta", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Egypt"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Niger?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British novelist wrote 'Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", 
      "Robinson Crusoe"
    ], 
    "question": "'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Samoa\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tonga", 
      "Vanuatu", 
      "Tuvalu"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Pacific Nation Gained Independence From New Zealand In 1962?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "rheumatic diseases, a branch of medicine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the nose and its diseases", 
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being", 
      "same as Aetiology", 
      "life in outer space", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "trees", 
      "angels", 
      "the medical study of the causation of disease"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Rheumatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toulouse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tolosa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Midnight Cowboy", 
      "Raging Bull"
    ], 
    "question": "The following is a line from which 1970's film 'you talkin to me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Stuarts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Tudors", 
      "The Plantagenets", 
      "The Lancasters"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Royal House Ruled England Between 1603 & 1714?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Hardy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Far From The Madding Crowd\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tongue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Heart", 
      "Biceps", 
      "Deltoids"
    ], 
    "question": "What organ is joined to the hyoid bone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Maggie Smith", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kathy Bates", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Elizabeth Banks", 
      "Susan Sarandon", 
      "Cameron Diaz", 
      "Amy Adams", 
      "Drew Barrymore", 
      "Uma Thurman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone and Gosford Park?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of X-Men: Days of Future Past?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Bhutan is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North Korea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "People's Republic of China shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Night Shift' was written by which American author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "La Paz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sucre", 
      "Santiago", 
      "Bogota"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Bolivia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Semitic cultures", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "plant diseases", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine", 
      "life", 
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "myths", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "primates"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Semitology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yamagata", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Takase?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Clarence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Terrence", 
      "Horace", 
      "Boris"
    ], 
    "question": "In the 1946 film, It's a Wonderful Life, what's the name of George Bailey's guardian angel?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1982", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1990", 
      "1971", 
      "1964"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Year Did The Falklands Conflict Begin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lithography", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Embography", 
      "Calligraphy", 
      "Recography"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the art of tracing designs and making impressions of them called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "300", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100", 
      "200", 
      "250"
    ], 
    "question": "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Meryl Streep", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cate Blanchett", 
      "Nicole Kidman", 
      "Natalie Portman", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Deer Hunter and Out of Africa feature which American actress?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Interstellar?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Dominica is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belarus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hungary", 
      "Austria", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Latvia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Romania", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Sweden", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Estonia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Moldova"
    ], 
    "question": "Poland shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Leo Tolstoy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Alexander Pushkin"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Death of Ivan Ilyich'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Tuor' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sense and Sensibility", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Candide", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Manon Lescaut", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1811, which piece of written work starts with the line 'The family of Dashwood had been long settled in Sussex.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Switzerland\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Netherlands", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Czech Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Has Borders With France, Germany, Austria, Lichtenstein & Italy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "the moon", 
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "the fetus, especially when within the uterus", 
      "dialects", 
      "human growth", 
      "prehistoric life"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Radiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Accra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kumasi"
    ], 
    "question": "'Cape Coast' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frank Capra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orson Welles", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Howard Hawks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed the 1946 classic 'It's A Wonderful Life'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tibet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country did China invade on Christmas day 1950", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Whistler", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andy Warhol", 
      "Grant Wood", 
      "Eddie Harold"
    ], 
    "question": "Which american artist is known for a portrait of his mother?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stainless Steel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aluminium", 
      "Einsteinium", 
      "Cast Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which metal was invented by British metallurgist Harold Brearley in 1912?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shigeru Miyamoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yu Suzuki", 
      "Satoru Iwata", 
      "Gunpei Yokoi"
    ], 
    "question": "Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Josh Brolin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Keanu Reeves"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Guardians of the Galaxy and No Country for Old Men?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Samoa is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lebanon", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Israel", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Oman"
    ], 
    "question": "Iraq shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "George R. R. Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Dreamsongs: A RRetrospective'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "Lady Catherine de Bourgh appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The A.B.C. Murders", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "Lolita", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "American Psycho (book)", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Crime and Punishment"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1936, which piece of written work starts with the line 'It was in June of 1935 that I came home from my ranch in South America for a stay of about six months.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thailand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ means \"land of the free.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "poisons", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "life", 
      "vibrations and oscillations in the Sun", 
      "the historical study of languages", 
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
      "the derivation of a persons character traits, by studying the shape of their skull", 
      "the ancient Egyptians", 
      "sleep"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Toxicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokkaichi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Tomida' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Friday the 13th", 
      "Scream", 
      "IT"
    ], 
    "question": "Which series of films features a habitual serial killer called Michael Myers", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malcolm X", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Martin Luther King", 
      "John F Kennedy", 
      "Lee Harvey Oswald"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was assassinated on Feb. 21, 1965?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "Anna Karenina"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Mr. Darcy' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ants", 
      "Grasshopper", 
      "Praying Mantis"
    ], 
    "question": "What insect has a type of hair on its eyes?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Ben Kingsley"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Sesame Street and King Kong?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed The Godfather Part II?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Palau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lebanon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cyprus", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Iran", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Greece", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Romania"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Syria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jules Verne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Victor Hugo", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Margaret Atwood", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Maurice Leblanc", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Guy de Maupassant", 
      "Arthur C. Clarke"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Tribulations of a Chinaman in China'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lolita", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "And Then There Were None", 
      "Ulysses", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Jin Ping Mei", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Slaughterhouse-Five", 
      "Justine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins.' This is the first line of which 1955 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Severn\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Thames", 
      "The Trent", 
      "The Wye"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Is The Longest River In Britain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "stalkers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "grasses", 
      "study of human characteristics", 
      "character", 
      "a branch of logic focusing on part-whole relationships", 
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "things of which we are by nature ignorant, or of things which cannot be known", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "the nature of values and value judgements"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Beierlology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ichihara", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Shizu' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Waterloo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trafalgar", 
      "Windsor", 
      "Dover"
    ], 
    "question": "Where was Napoleon defeated?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Peter Rabbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Watership Down", 
      "Winny The Pooh", 
      "Black Beauty"
    ], 
    "question": "What story features flopsy, mopsy and cottontail?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Frontal Lobe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cortex", 
      "The Hypothalamus", 
      "The Parietal Lobe"
    ], 
    "question": "What Part Of The Brain Is Affected In A Lobotomy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Six", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Eight", 
      "Two"
    ], 
    "question": "How many pockets does a snooker table have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ken Jeong", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "John Turturro"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Community and Avengers: Endgame feature which American comedian, actor and physician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert Zemeckis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Forrest Gump?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Togo", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Mali", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Libya", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Nigeria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Ivan Turgenev"
    ], 
    "question": "'Twice-Told Tales' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Great Gatsby", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Two households, both alike in dignity, in fair Verona, where we lay our scene, from ancient grudge break to new mutiny, where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Syria", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Iraq"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Holiday Resort Bodrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "plants; botany", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "wonders, or monsters", 
      "the study or knowledge of emetics", 
      "nutrition", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
      "myths"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phytology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aomori", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takada' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spilled champagne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A lightning strike", 
      "Divine intervention", 
      "A plutonium power core"
    ], 
    "question": "What caused the computer in Electric Dreams to become alive?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles II", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "James II", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "During Which King's Reign Did The Great Fire Of London Occur?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Men", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Grown Women", 
      "Old Women", 
      "Out in the Barlows"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the sequel to Louisa May Alcott's \"Little Women\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "11 days", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "11 weeks", 
      "11 hours", 
      "11 months"
    ], 
    "question": "Adult polar bears usually eat just the skin and blubber of a seal. They leave the meat for cubs and scavengers. One seal will sustain an adult bear for __________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "Three", 
      "Four"
    ], 
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nicole Kidman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Natalie Portman", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Moulin Rouge! and Aquaman feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Guinea-Bissau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uganda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Djibouti", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Israel", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus"
    ], 
    "question": "Sudan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Umberto Eco", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Orhan Pamuk", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Jos\u00e9 Saramago", 
      "Paulo Coelho", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Prince and the Pauper", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "The Red and the Black", 
      "A Tale of Two Cities", 
      "Charlotte's Web", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'I will set down a tale as it was told to me by one who had it of his father, which latter had it of HIS father, this last having in like manner had it of HIS father\u2014and so on, back and still back, three hundred years and more, the fathers transmitting it to the sons and so preserving it.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mogadishu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timbuktu", 
      "Bakar", 
      "Addis Ababa"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Somalia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the relationship between electric phenomena and bodily processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "ligaments", 
      "the future", 
      "demons", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "illness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Electrophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kaliningrad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Moscow", 
      "Saint Petersburg", 
      "Kazan", 
      "Yekaterinburg", 
      "Ufa", 
      "Rostov-on-Don", 
      "Nizhny Novgorod", 
      "Novosibirsk", 
      "Saratov", 
      "Voronezh"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called K\u00f6nigsberg?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chevy Chase", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "Tom Hanks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1916", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1900", 
      "1945", 
      "1933"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was The Berlin Wall Erected?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spanish", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Portuguese", 
      "Mexican", 
      "Andorran"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the nationality of Picasso?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gall bladder", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kidney", 
      "Bowel", 
      "Spleen"
    ], 
    "question": "This organ is a small pouch that stores bile.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Long Jump", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "High Jump", 
      "Triple Jump", 
      "Pole Vault"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Jump Event Did Carl Lewis Specialize In As Well As The Sprint?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert Mitchum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peter O'Toole", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Richard Burton", 
      "Tim Curry", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Michael Ironside"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Longest Day and Cape Fear feature which American film actor, author, composer and singer (1917-1997)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Luc Besson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Lucy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Liechtenstein is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Chile", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Brazil shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Karel \u010capek", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "William Gibson", 
      "Maurice Leblanc", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "Stanis\u0142aw Lem", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin"
    ], 
    "question": "'Krakatit' was written by which Czech writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Neville Longbottom' appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Great Gatsby", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Two households, both alike in dignity, in fair Verona, where we lay our scene, from ancient grudge break to new mutiny, where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mali", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Senegal"
    ], 
    "question": "The City Of Timbuktu Is In Which African Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the mnemonic practice of writing sentences such that the numbers of letters in the words correspond to the consecutive digits of pi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric climates", 
      "hearing; a branch of medicine", 
      "crime", 
      "rocks", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "bees", 
      "viruses", 
      "the Shroud of Turin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Piphilology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mikkeli", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Ristiina?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Blues Brothers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sister Act", 
      "National Lampoon's Vacation", 
      "Animal House"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Comedy Film Does Aretha Franklin Star As A Proprietress Of A Soul Food Joint? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crete", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Babylon", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tarzan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiderman", 
      "Scooby Doo", 
      "Buggs Bunny"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous character did Edgar Rice Burroughs create?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sciatic nerve", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Optic nerve", 
      "Lumbar plexus", 
      "Ulnar nerve"
    ], 
    "question": "Which is the largest nerve in the Human Body?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "16", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12", 
      "10", 
      "14"
    ], 
    "question": "How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bill Hader", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Saturday Night Live and The BFG?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of X-Men: Apocalypse?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Suriname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sweden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poland", 
      "Finland", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Romania", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Austria", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Montenegro"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Latvia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Beatrix Potter"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Case-Book of Sherlock Holmes' was written by which Scottish physician and author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Return of the King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Hobbit"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pippin looked out from the shelter of Gandalf's coat.' This is the first line of which 1955 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greece", 
      "Italy", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "There are sand dunes in Arcachon, ___________ that are 350 feet high.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the characteristics of the skull", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wonders, or monsters", 
      "dietetics", 
      "angels", 
      "blood", 
      "a parody of astrology", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics", 
      "children's behavior and development"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Craniology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hiratsuka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Suba?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Persia\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Parthia", 
      "Mesopotamia", 
      "Assyria"
    ], 
    "question": "Prior to 1935 what was Iran known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Naive art", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beginner's art", 
      "Natural art", 
      "Pop art"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the art style, usually paintings, characterized by a simplified style, nonscientific perspective, and bold colors. The artists are generally not professionally trained.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hertz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Watt", 
      "Pascal"
    ], 
    "question": "What are the units of measurement for Frequency?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "110m Hurdles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pole Vault", 
      "Discus", 
      "Steeple Chase"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Athletic Event Was Colin Jackson A Dominant Figure?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frances Fisher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Grey's Anatomy and The X-Files feature which English-born American actress?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of The Dark Knight?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Tonga is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Myanmar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Laos", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Oman", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kazakhstan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders India?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephenie Meyer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Brandon Sanderson", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Mark Twain", 
      "John Green"
    ], 
    "question": "'Eclipse' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Study in Scarlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd", 
      "The Shadow of the Wind", 
      "Inferno", 
      "The A.B.C. Murders", 
      "Angels & Demons", 
      "The Da Vinci Code", 
      "The Lost Symbol", 
      "The Caves of Steel"
    ], 
    "question": "'In the year 1878 I took my degree of Doctor of Medicine of the University of London, and proceeded to Netley to go through the course prescribed for surgeons in the army.' This is the first line of which 1887 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rushmore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yellowstone", 
      "Everest", 
      "Fairweather"
    ], 
    "question": "On what mountain are four presidents' faces carved? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "vocal sounds", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
      "childbirth, sometimes spelled", 
      "very low temperatures and related phenomena", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "plankton", 
      "the effect of evolution on ethology", 
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors", 
      "paranormal or psychic phenomenon that defy conventional scientific explanations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phonology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yl\u00f6j\u00e4rvi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Viljakkala' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "White Christmas", 
      "The Holly & The Ivy"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Film Which First Featured Bing Crosby's Song 'White Christmas''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo and Juliet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Othello", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "What shakespearean play features the line: \"A plague on both your houses\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Milky way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andromedu", 
      "Ursa", 
      "Orion"
    ], 
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known called _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dustin Hoffman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Brian Cox"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Rain Man and Kramer vs. Kramer feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 2?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Marshall Islands is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Benin", 
      "Niger", 
      "Togo", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Mali", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Angola", 
      "Libya", 
      "Burundi"
    ], 
    "question": "Cameroon shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry James", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Robert Louis Stevenson", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Salman Rushdie", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Philip Reeve", 
      "Douglas Adams", 
      "L. Frank Baum", 
      "Christopher Tolkien"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Turn of the Screw'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Neville Longbottom' appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
      "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
      "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "'It was nearing midnight and the Prime Minister was sitting alone in his office, reading a long memo that was slipping through his brain without leaving the lightest trace of meaning behind.' This is the first line of which 2005 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cambodia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thailand", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Laos", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Philippines"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country is the Mekong River Delta", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "writing systems", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the field of dermatological anatomical pathology", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "existence", 
      "the belief system/cult religion founded by L", 
      "the scientific study of baths, bathing and of their application to disease", 
      "the preparation of books and manuscripts", 
      "demons", 
      "snakes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Grammatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madrid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barcelona", 
      "Valencia", 
      "Seville", 
      "Bilbao", 
      "Zaragoza", 
      "Reus", 
      "Palma de Mallorca", 
      "Pamplona", 
      "Granada", 
      "A Coru\u00f1a"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Carabanchel Alto?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Reginald Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Wayne Gacey Jr", 
      "Ted Bundy", 
      "Ed Gaine"
    ], 
    "question": "Which notorious murderer, hanged in July 1953, had his story told in the film \"Ten Rillington Place\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harold Wilson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Clement Atlee", 
      "Anthony Eden", 
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The British Prime Minister Between 1964 & 1969?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "As You Like It", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Twelfth Night", 
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "Richard III"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Shakespearean play is set in the forest of Arden?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Hudson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Isambard Kingdom Brunel", 
      "Robert Stephenson", 
      "Thomas Telford"
    ], 
    "question": "In The 19th Century Who Was The Railway King?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Long Jump", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "High Jump", 
      "Triple Jump", 
      "Pole Vault"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Jump Event Did Carl Lewis Specialize In As Well As The Sprint?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mark Wahlberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Ryan Reynolds"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Departed and Ted?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Raiders of the Lost Ark?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Marshall Islands is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Afghanistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Oman", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Myanmar"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Pakistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter' was written by which British novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", 
      "Robinson Crusoe"
    ], 
    "question": "'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;' This is the first line of which 1908 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uruguay", 
      "Paraguay", 
      "Peru", 
      "Argentina", 
      "Chile"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country is the most lowest (sea level) point of South America?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "geology of celestial bodies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "museum management", 
      "bones", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "bacteria", 
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair", 
      "ancient multicelled plants", 
      "though not an -ology, is a commemoration of a person's life at his/her funeral"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Astrogeology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "L\u00e9vis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Toronto", 
      "Montreal", 
      "Ottawa", 
      "Vancouver", 
      "Edmonton", 
      "Quebec City", 
      "Winnipeg", 
      "Calgary", 
      "Hamilton", 
      "London"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Les Chutes-de-la-Chaudi\u00e8re Regional County Municipality?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jingle All The Way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Santa Clause", 
      "Miracle on 34th Street", 
      "Bad Santa"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Popular Christmas Movie Featured A Must Have Toy Called 'Turbo Man''", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Melmac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barnzac", 
      "Tonzac", 
      "Fardac"
    ], 
    "question": "What planet was 'ALF' from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Hardy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Far From The Madding Crowd\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edward Jenner", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Francis Crick", 
      "Edith Bower", 
      "Marcel Decroix"
    ], 
    "question": "Who developed the vaccine for smallpox?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Six", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Eight", 
      "Two"
    ], 
    "question": "How many pockets does a snooker table have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Jack Nicholson", 
      "Charlton Heston", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Dustin Hoffman", 
      "Josh Brolin", 
      "Danny Glover", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Adam Sandler"
    ], 
    "question": "Which French actor has starred in films including Life of Pi and La Vie en Rose?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Pulp Fiction?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Dominica is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bolivia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Panama", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Paraguay", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Argentina", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Peru?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English writer and social critic wrote 'The Pickwick Papers'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jane Eyre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "Little Women", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The Red and the Black"
    ], 
    "question": "'There was no possibility of taking a walk that day.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aluminium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxygen", 
      "Silicon", 
      "Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which element makes up 8.13% of the Earth's crust", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "periodic biological phenomena such as flowering, migration, breeding, etc", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "non-terrestrial life", 
      "religion", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "prehistoric life", 
      "the study and analysis of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "study of refuse and trash", 
      "rocks"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Reims", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called La Neuvillette?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jason", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie", 
      "Mike", 
      "Chuckie"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Bad Guy In The Friday The 13th Series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "Mexico", 
      "The Bahamas"
    ], 
    "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joanne Kathleen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Julia Kathleen", 
      "Joanne Katherine", 
      "Julia Katherine"
    ], 
    "question": "What do the initials \"JK\" stand for in the name \"JK Rowling\", Author of the \"Harry Potter\" books?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Acidity Or Alkalinity", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Radiation", 
      "Wind Speed", 
      "Gravity"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is PH A Measure Of", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aberdeen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rangers", 
      "Celtic", 
      "Hearts"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scottish Football Club Boasted The First All Seater Football Stadium In Britain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ewan McGregor", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert Downey Jr.", 
      "Robin Williams", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "George Clooney", 
      "Laurence Fishburne", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Brad Pitt", 
      "James Franco", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Beauty and the Beast and Star Wars: Episode I \u2013 The Phantom Menace feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Lumet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of 12 Angry Men?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Dominica is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Benin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nigeria", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Mali", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Niger", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Chad"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fyodor Dostoyevsky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vladimir Nabokov", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Nikolai Gogol", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Alexander Pushkin", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Mikhail Lermontov"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Idiot'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Mockingjay", 
      "Eclipse"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mr and Mrs Dursley, of number four, Privet Drive, were proud to say that they were perfectly normal, thank you very much.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Manila\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jakarta", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Bandung"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Is The Capital Of The Philippines?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the moon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a synonym for taxonomy", 
      "heat", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "reptiles and amphibians", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study or exploration of caves", 
      "sleep"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Selenology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fujisawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shibuya?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pre-Raphaelite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neo-Raphaelite", 
      "Pre-Jacobian", 
      "Neo-Jacobian"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of English painters formed in 1848. These artists attempted to recapture an old style of painting. They rejected industrialized England and focused on painting from nature, producing detailed, colorful works. What were they called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Central America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Africa", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Japan"
    ], 
    "question": "Where Is The Natural Habitat Of The Cheese Plant?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Jordan", 
      "Yao Ming", 
      "Kobe Bryant"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the NBA MVP in 1976, 77, and 80?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Donald Sutherland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alec Baldwin", 
      "Laurence Fishburne", 
      "George Clooney", 
      "Ben Affleck", 
      "James Franco", 
      "Sean Connery", 
      "Gary Oldman", 
      "Robert Downey Jr.", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Canadian actor has starred in films including The Hunger Games and Ordinary People?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stanley Kubrick", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of 2001: A Space Odyssey?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Andorra is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kyrgyzstan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "People's Republic of China shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Edgar Allan Poe", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Insomnia' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuor appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.' This is the first line of which 1871 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belize", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guatemala", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest North?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "angels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "numbers", 
      "religion", 
      "Semitic cultures", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "the Assyrians", 
      "things in order of time or time", 
      "the study and the art of bell ringing", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Angelology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yamagata", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takase' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Jones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Jackson", 
      "John Jones", 
      "Jim Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Who led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Men", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Grown Women", 
      "Old Women", 
      "Out in the Barlows"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the sequel to Louisa May Alcott's \"Little Women\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pelican", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Flamingo", 
      "Tiger"
    ], 
    "question": "A __________ consumes about 33 percent of its body weight in a single meal.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "1970's", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1960's", 
      "1950's", 
      "1940's"
    ], 
    "question": "In which decade was cricket's first World Cup Final played?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "James Hong", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actor, voice actor and director has starred in films including Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. and Chuck?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bryan Singer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed X-Men: Apocalypse?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Palau?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Switzerland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Poland", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Albania", 
      "Belgium", 
      "North Macedonia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Austria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows' was written by which British novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Through the Looking-Glass", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mio, My Son", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Heidi", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'One thing was certain, that the white kitten had had nothing to do with it: \u2014 it was the black kitten\u2019s fault entirely.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colorado", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mississippi", 
      "Hudson", 
      "Rio Grande"
    ], 
    "question": "Which river made The Grand Canyon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a branch of logic focusing on part-whole relationships", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "karyotypes", 
      "drugs", 
      "the mental processes within mental illness or disorders", 
      "ants", 
      "the mathematical study of closeness and connectedness", 
      "the cosmos or our place in it", 
      "drugs", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Mereology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kasugai", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takaki' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oklahoma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Missouri", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US state in 1907 was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rembrandt", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vermeer", 
      "Van Gogh", 
      "Monet"
    ], 
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vacuum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dark Matter", 
      "Black Hole", 
      "White Hole"
    ], 
    "question": "What term appies to space devoid of matter? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kevin Bacon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include The Following and Apollo 13?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Columbus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Saint Kitts and Nevis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mozambique", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malawi", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Mauritius", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Djibouti"
    ], 
    "question": "Comoros shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Umberto Eco", 
      "S\u00f8ren Kierkegaard", 
      "Orhan Pamuk", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Jos\u00e9 Saramago", 
      "Paulo Coelho", 
      "Jonathan Swift", 
      "Voltaire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote '1Q84 Buch 1 & 2 (2012 btb ed.)'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Game of Thrones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Silver Chair", 
      "The Amber Spyglass", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "Gulliver's Travels"
    ], 
    "question": "'\u201cWe should start back,\u201d Gared urged as the woods began to grow dark around them.' This is the first line of which 1996 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mount Kilimanjaro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mount Kenya", 
      "Mount Mawazi", 
      "Mount Ngaliema"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the highest mountain in Africa.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the relationship between electric phenomena and bodily processes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "the practice of escaping from restraints or other traps", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "ligaments", 
      "the future", 
      "demons", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "illness"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Electrophysiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oslo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bergen", 
      "Trondheim", 
      "Kongsvinger", 
      "T\u00f8nsberg", 
      "Narvik"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Christiania?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "160", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "0", 
      "50", 
      "300"
    ], 
    "question": "Approximately how many children did pharaoh Ramses II father?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boys", 
      "Witches", 
      "Game"
    ], 
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's _________\".", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hertz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joule", 
      "Watt", 
      "Pascal"
    ], 
    "question": "What are the units of measurement for Frequency?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Orange", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue", 
      "Yellow", 
      "Red"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Grade Follows A Yellow Belt In Judo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kathy Bates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Emma Thompson", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Naomi Watts"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Two and a Half Men and Titanic feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Lean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Lawrence of Arabia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Belize is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Azerbaijan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Georgia", 
      "Syria", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Israel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Iran?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Walter Scott", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Alice Munro", 
      "Philip Reeve", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "Victor Hugo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scottish historical novelist, playwright, and poet wrote 'The Heart of Midlothian'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ottawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Toronto", 
      "Montreal", 
      "Vancouver", 
      "Winnipeg", 
      "Calgary"
    ], 
    "question": "The city name ________________ is derived from an Algonquin word meaning \"traders.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the future", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "flow", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "drugs", 
      "museum management", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "a branch of geology that studies sediments", 
      "ticks and mites", 
      "gross and disgusting things"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Futurology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hobart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sydney", 
      "Melbourne", 
      "Brisbane", 
      "Adelaide", 
      "Canberra", 
      "Perth", 
      "Geelong", 
      "Newcastle", 
      "Launceston", 
      "Ballarat"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Settlement of Sullivans Cove?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crete", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Babylon", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dr Zhivago", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lolita", 
      "The Brothers Karamazov", 
      "The Cherry Orchard"
    ], 
    "question": "For which novel was Boris Pasternak awarded the 1958 Nobel Prize, an award he declined?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Salmon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tuna", 
      "Trout", 
      "Cod"
    ], 
    "question": "Atlantic __________ are able to leap 15 feet high.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saints", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gators", 
      "Rockets", 
      "Brass"
    ], 
    "question": "American Football: The New Orleans __________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Travolta", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Ryan Reynolds"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Pulp Fiction and Hairspray feature which American actor, dancer and singer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Laos is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Oman", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Myanmar"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Pakistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gustave Flaubert", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anatole France", 
      "Guy de Maupassant", 
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Alexandre Dumas", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Victor Hugo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Bouvard et P\u00e9cuchet' was written by which French writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Little Women", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Candide", 
      "The Neverending Story"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line ''Christmas won't be Christmas without any presents''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the largest island in the Caribbean?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "male health and disease", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animal behaviour", 
      "the medical study of the causation of disease", 
      "the structure of diseased tissues", 
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "human growth", 
      "animal behaviour", 
      "fungi", 
      "viruses"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Andrology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokosuka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nagai?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Marathon Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Rain Man", 
      "Tootsie"
    ], 
    "question": "In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character ' Babe Levy'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aesop", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Homer", 
      "Plato", 
      "Odysseus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Ancient Greek writer was famous for his Fables?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Absolute Zero", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freezing Point", 
      "Mitchell's number", 
      "Equilibrium"
    ], 
    "question": "What is -459.7 F also know as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catcher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pitcher", 
      "Guard", 
      "Steer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Audrey Hepburn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bette Davis", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Selena Gomez", 
      "Catherine Keener", 
      "Jane Fonda", 
      "Zoe Saldana", 
      "Angela Bassett", 
      "Mare Winningham", 
      "Sarah Jessica Parker", 
      "Jennifer Lawrence"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Roman Holiday and Breakfast at Tiffany's feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Burton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Batman Returns?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Palau is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Japan", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Laos", 
      "Palau", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "North Korea shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Asimov", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Stephen King", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "Frank Herbert", 
      "William Gibson", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "Robert Silverberg"
    ], 
    "question": "'Foundation\u2019s Edge' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "New Moon", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mont Blanc\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mount Etna", 
      "Elbrus", 
      "Grossglockner"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Highest Mountain In The Alps?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "living tissues", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "angels", 
      "prehistoric environments by analyzing fossils and rock strata", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the historical study of languages", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "a variant of physiognomy", 
      "the study of picture postcards"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Histology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Trois-Rivi\u00e8res", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Toronto", 
      "Montreal", 
      "Ottawa", 
      "Vancouver", 
      "Edmonton", 
      "Quebec City", 
      "Winnipeg", 
      "Calgary", 
      "Hamilton", 
      "London"
    ], 
    "question": "'Trois-Rivi\u00e8res-Ouest, Quebec' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chevy Chase", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steve Martin", 
      "Tim Allen", 
      "Tom Hanks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the lead role of the accident prone Clark Griswold in the 1989 'National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hoover", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin", 
      "Roosevelt", 
      "Johnson"
    ], 
    "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The City & the City", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Thorin' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Puffin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Albatross", 
      "Penguin", 
      "Dodo"
    ], 
    "question": "What bird is associated with Lundy Island?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blackburn Rovers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Manchester United", 
      "Arsenal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which was the second club to win the English Premier League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joaquin Phoenix", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peter O'Toole", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Tim Curry", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Richard Burton", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Anthony Quinn"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Joker and Her feature which American actor, music video director, producer, musician, and social activist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Peter Jackson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Marshall Islands is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Zambia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Botswana", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Malawi", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Lesotho"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Angola?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "William Shakespeare", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arthur C. Clarke", 
      "Isaac Newton", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Lee Child", 
      "John le Carr\u00e9", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "J. K. Rowling"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English playwright and poet wrote 'Richard III'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Neville Longbottom' appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlotte's Web", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Justine", 
      "One Thousand and One Nights", 
      "Catch-22", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "Carmilla"
    ], 
    "question": "'Alice was beginning to get very tired of sitting by her sister on the bank, and of having nothing to do: once or twice she had peeped into the book her sister was reading, but it had no pictures or conversations in it, \u201cand what is the use of a book,\u201d thought Alice, \u201cwithout pictures or conversations?\u201d' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mississippi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arkansas", 
      "Alabama", 
      "Louisiana"
    ], 
    "question": "In which state is the Natchez Trail?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "study of devil worshipers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study", 
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the nature of values and value judgements", 
      "present-day landforms, traditionally on Earth but with increasing frequency on nearby planetary objects", 
      "animal diseases", 
      "bacteria", 
      "anesthesia and anesthetics; a branch of medicine", 
      "a parody of astrology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Chavezology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "N\u00eemes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nemausus' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Concorde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Channel Tunnel", 
      "Eurostar", 
      "An animal cloning plant"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1962, for what did Britain and France sign an agreement to build together?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joanne Kathleen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Julia Kathleen", 
      "Joanne Katherine", 
      "Julia Katherine"
    ], 
    "question": "What do the initials \"JK\" stand for in the name \"JK Rowling\", Author of the \"Harry Potter\" books?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "206", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "310", 
      "233", 
      "280"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Bones Are There In The Adult Human Body?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fourteen", 
      "Thirteen", 
      "Twelve"
    ], 
    "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Danny Trejo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Donald Sutherland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include The X-Files and NCIS: Los Angeles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Pulp Fiction?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Guinea-Bissau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Norway", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poland", 
      "Lithuania", 
      "Latvia", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Germany", 
      "Estonia", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Austria", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Belarus", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Croatia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Sweden?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alexander Pushkin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nikolai Gogol", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Astrid Lindgren", 
      "Marquis de Sade", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Joseph Conrad"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Queen of Spades' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The War of the Worlds", 
      "Northern Lights", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "Planet of the Apes", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "I Am Legend", 
      "The Amber Spyglass"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Far out in the uncharted backwaters of the unfashionable end of the western spiral arm of the Galaxy lies a small, unregarded yellow sun.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Syria", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Iraq"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Holiday Resort Bodrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the eyes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "bacteria", 
      "crayfish", 
      "signs", 
      "myths", 
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "animals", 
      "mountains and their mapping", 
      "the purported influences of celestial bodies on earthly affairs"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ophthalmology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin", 
      "Wuhan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Khanbaliq?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alaska", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Puerto Rico", 
      "New Mexico"
    ], 
    "question": "In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pre-Raphaelite", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neo-Raphaelite", 
      "Pre-Jacobian", 
      "Neo-Jacobian"
    ], 
    "question": "A group of English painters formed in 1848. These artists attempted to recapture an old style of painting. They rejected industrialized England and focused on painting from nature, producing detailed, colorful works. What were they called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jurassic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesozoic", 
      "Triassic", 
      "Devonian"
    ], 
    "question": "In Geology What Period followed The Cretaceous?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sean Penn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Jim Carrey"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Two and a Half Men and Milk feature which American actor, screenwriter, and film director?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Solo: A Star Wars Story?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Mauritius is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bolivia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peru", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Panama", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda"
    ], 
    "question": "Argentina shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "Joseph Conrad"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Knights of the Cross' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Neville Longbottom' appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Twist", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Germinal", 
      "Eine Geschichte des Universums in 100 Sternen", 
      "Madame Bovary", 
      "The Decameron", 
      "Buddenbrooks", 
      "The Snow Queen", 
      "The Art of War", 
      "A Dance with Dragons"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Among other public buildings in a certain town, which for many reasons it will be prudent to refrain from mentioning, and to which I will assign no fictitious name, there is one anciently common to most towns, great or small: to wit, a workhouse; and in this workhouse was born; on a day and date which I need not trouble myself to repeat, inasmuch as it can be of no possible consequence to the'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cape Town\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freetown", 
      "Johannesburg", 
      "Port Elizabeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What was The First Town Founded By Europeans In Southern Africa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "beetles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the Shroud of Turin", 
      "angels", 
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms", 
      "bees", 
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "flags", 
      "gemstones and ornamental materials", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Coleopterology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "\u014csaka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nakashima?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jason", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Freddie", 
      "Mike", 
      "Chuckie"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Bad Guy In The Friday The 13th Series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dwight Eisenhower", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Franklin Roosevelt", 
      "Lyndon Johnson", 
      "Jimmy Carter"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was President of the USA from 1953 till 1961?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Pratchett", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Brandon Sanderson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author penned the Discworld Series of sci-fi novels?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Heart", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul", 
      "Blood"
    ], 
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eight", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Twelve", 
      "Sixteen"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Lanes Does An Olympic Standard Swimming Pool Have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russell Crowe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "John Wayne", 
      "Ron Perlman", 
      "Frank Welker", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Kevin Spacey", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Billy Bob Thornton", 
      "Jon Favreau"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Gladiator and A Beautiful Mind?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Bhutan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uzbekistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Oman", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "India", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Afghanistan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. Rider Haggard", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Virginia Woolf", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "George Orwell", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Arthur Conan Doyle"
    ], 
    "question": "'Ozymandias' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Game of Thrones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Silver Chair", 
      "The Amber Spyglass", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "Gulliver's Travels"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line '\u201cWe should start back,\u201d Gared urged as the woods began to grow dark around them.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Denver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "grasses", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "museum management", 
      "the nature and origins of knowledge", 
      "birds", 
      "the effects of climate on living organisms", 
      "cats", 
      "animals"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cetology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokosuka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nagai?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ming", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qin", 
      "Han", 
      "Tang"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fourteen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Six", 
      "Twelve"
    ], 
    "question": "How many lines are in a sonnet?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Solid Carbon Dioxide", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Solid Methane", 
      "Solid Helium", 
      "Solid Oxygen"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is Dry Ice?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Inky, Pinky, Blinky & Clyde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Inky, Pinky, Blinky & Floyd", 
      "Dinky, Pinky, Winky & Clyde", 
      "Dinky, Pinky, Blinky & Floyd"
    ], 
    "question": "What Are The Names Of The Ghosts In The Classic 80's Video Game Pac Man? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kevin Bacon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Apollo 13 and X-Men: First Class?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Raiders of the Lost Ark?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Bahrain is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nepal", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "People's Republic of China shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "George R. R. Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'A Song of Ice and Fire' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Tuor' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Sea of Monsters", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "The Titan's Curse", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.' This is the first line of which 2007 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aluminium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxygen", 
      "Silicon", 
      "Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which element makes up 8.13% of the Earth's crust", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the medical study of the causation of disease", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "poisons", 
      "schematic layouts", 
      "men", 
      "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows", 
      "the practical arts", 
      "genetic differences in relation to the environment", 
      "the ear and throat; a branch of medicine", 
      "ends or final causes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Aetiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nagano", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Yoshida?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Clarence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Terrence", 
      "Horace", 
      "Boris"
    ], 
    "question": "In the 1946 film, It's a Wonderful Life, what's the name of George Bailey's guardian angel?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ming", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qin", 
      "Han", 
      "Tang"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Henry VI", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard III", 
      "Othello", 
      "Macbeth"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Shakespeare's first play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Milky way", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andromedu", 
      "Ursa", 
      "Orion"
    ], 
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known called _________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Hingis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Serena Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova", 
      "Steffi Graf"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Female Tennis Star Was Handed A Two Year Ban After Testing Positive For Cocaine At Wimbledon In 2007?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jim Carrey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Pierce Brosnan", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Javier Bardem", 
      "Brian Cox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Mask and The Truman Show?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Nauru is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Montenegro", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Malta", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Italy", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Libya", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Austria"
    ], 
    "question": "Greece shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vladimir Nabokov", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Kurt Vonnegut", 
      "Mikhail Bulgakov", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Thomas Mann", 
      "Herman Melville", 
      "Frank Herbert", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Nikolai Gogol"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Russian-American novelist, lepidopterist, professor wrote 'Lolita (2010 Penguin Classics ed.)'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book series does the character 'Neville Longbottom' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Two Towers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Last Battle"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Aragorn sped on up the hill.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venezuela", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Peru", 
      "Bolivia"
    ], 
    "question": "What country's capital is Caracas?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "hair and scalp", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "angels", 
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "sleep", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "China", 
      "plants; botany", 
      "the relationship of biological or other phenomena to their locations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Trichology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sendai", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takasago' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dances With Wolves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Total Recall", 
      "Edward Scissorhands", 
      "Pretty Woman"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 1990 Movie Which Won John Barry An Oscar For Best Film Score", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Cromwell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII", 
      "Francis Drake", 
      "Elizabeth I"
    ], 
    "question": "Who banned Christmas in Britain in 1647?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Hardy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Austen", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "Who wrote \"Far From The Madding Crowd\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "hours", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "days", 
      "minutes", 
      "nights"
    ], 
    "question": "The snail mates only once in its entire life. When it does mate, however, it may take as long as 12 _______ to consummate the act.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Queensbury Rules", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Lonsdale Rules", 
      "The McArthur Rules", 
      "The Pugil Rules"
    ], 
    "question": "In Boxing, Fighting With Gloves Became Standard In 1867 After The Formulation Of Which Set Of Rules?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pierce Brosnan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme", 
      "John Turturro", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "Russell Crowe", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Michael Fassbender", 
      "Ryan Reynolds"
    ], 
    "question": "The films GoldenEye and The World Is Not Enough feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Interstellar?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Eswatini?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Laos", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Thailand", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "India", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Palau", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "North Korea", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Vietnam shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "L. Frank Baum", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Suzanne Collins", 
      "James Fenimore Cooper", 
      "Donna Leon", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Poul Anderson", 
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Cassandra Clare", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "F. Scott Fitzgerald"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Wonderful Wizard of Oz' was written by which American children's writer, editor, journalist, screenwriter (1856-1919)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuor appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Two Towers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Life, the Universe and Everything", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Last Battle"
    ], 
    "question": "'Aragorn sped on up the hill.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venice\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Ulaanbaatar"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Is Marco Polo Airport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "making timepieces, measuring time and timekeeping", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "animals", 
      "venereal diseases", 
      "ends or final causes", 
      "the purported influences of celestial bodies on earthly affairs", 
      "books, printing, and publishing; also called Bibliography", 
      "character", 
      "blackberries", 
      "venereal diseases"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Horology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Siegen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Berlin", 
      "Munich", 
      "Hamburg", 
      "Leipzig", 
      "Dresden", 
      "Nuremberg", 
      "Hanover", 
      "Stuttgart", 
      "Cologne", 
      "Frankfurt am Main"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Buschgotthardsh\u00fctten?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Texas Chansaw Massacre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halloween", 
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "The Exorcist"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Horror Film Would You Associate The Character Leatherface? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catherine Of Aragon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anne Boleyn", 
      "Anne Howard", 
      "Catherine Parr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Percy Bysshe Shelley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anthony Byron Shelley", 
      "Henry Mark Shelley", 
      "Harvey Butler Shelley"
    ], 
    "question": "This Romantic poet and husband of Mary Shelley drowned in a boating accident?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Structure of Cells", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blood", 
      "Code-Breaking", 
      "Cloud Formations"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cytology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barcelona", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "London", 
      "Paris"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1992 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Fassbender", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gerard Butler", 
      "Jim Carrey", 
      "Robert Redford", 
      "Hugh Jackman", 
      "Ryan Reynolds", 
      "Seth Rogen", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Billy Bob Thornton", 
      "Bradley Cooper", 
      "Russell Crowe"
    ], 
    "question": "The films X-Men: Days of Future Past and Inglourious Basterds feature which German-born Irish actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Lucas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Star Wars?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of San Marino is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Chile", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Brazil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thomas Mann", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "F. Scott Fitzgerald", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Isabel Allende", 
      "Robert Silverberg", 
      "Stephenie Meyer", 
      "Frederik Pohl", 
      "Cassandra Clare", 
      "George R. R. Martin", 
      "Karel \u010capek", 
      "Ayn Rand"
    ], 
    "question": "'Joseph and His Brothers' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dracula", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "'Salem's Lot", 
      "Carrie", 
      "World War Z", 
      "The Shining", 
      "Les Liaisons dangereuses", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "I Am Legend"
    ], 
    "question": "'3 May. Bistritz. - Left Munich at 8.35 p.m. on 1st May, arriving at Vienna early next Morning; should have arrived at 6.46, but train was an hour late.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bangladesh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "India", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Laos", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Cambodia"
    ], 
    "question": "___________ is the most densely populated non_island region in the world, with more than 1,970 humans per square mile.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "things of which we are by nature ignorant, or of things which cannot be known", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the interrelationships between living organisms and their environment", 
      "nerves", 
      "algae", 
      "puzzles", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine", 
      "medicine relating to women, or of women in general", 
      "symptoms"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Agnoiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fukui", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nishiago' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Halloween", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Nightmare on Elm Street", 
      "Scream", 
      "Child's Play"
    ], 
    "question": "The Character Of Mike Myers Features Heavily In Which Series Of Horror Movies?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "What country did the allies invade in World War II's Operation Avalanche? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Foreshortening", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Isometric Projection", 
      "Topomorphism", 
      "Skewed Perspective"
    ], 
    "question": "Which art technique can be described as \"Reducing or distorting in order to represent three-dimensional space as perceived by the eye\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jurassic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesozoic", 
      "Triassic", 
      "Devonian"
    ], 
    "question": "In Geology What Period followed The Cretaceous?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southpaw", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goofy", 
      "Regular", 
      "Orthodox"
    ], 
    "question": "What Do You Call A Boxer Who Leads With Their Right? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Hopkins", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Thor and The Silence of the Lambs feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roland Emmerich", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Independence Day?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Samoa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Seychelles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malawi", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Mauritius", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Djibouti"
    ], 
    "question": "Comoros shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Neil Gaiman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Douglas Adams", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "J. K. Rowling"
    ], 
    "question": "'Coraline' was written by which English fantasy writer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuor appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kidnapped", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Gargantua and Pantagruel"
    ], 
    "question": "'You don\u2019t know about me without you have read a book by the name of The Adventures of Tom Sawyer; but that ain't no matter. That book was made by Mr. Mark Twain, and he told the truth, mainly. There were things which he stretched, but mainly he told the truth. That is nothing. I never seen anybody but lied one time or another, without it was Aunt Polly, or the widow, or maybe Mary.' This is the first line of which 1884 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vietnam", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Philippines"
    ], 
    "question": "In which country is the Mekong River Delta?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "dogs", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the ecology of plant communities", 
      "drug dosage", 
      "Church architecture and decoration, or separately the Christian Church", 
      "the ancient Egyptians", 
      "religion", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "pollen"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Cynology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fukui", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nishiago?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pennsylvania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ohio", 
      "Maryland", 
      "Delaware"
    ], 
    "question": "In which American state is George A. Romero's 1968 film 'Night Of The Living Dead' set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Capricorn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gemini", 
      "Aries", 
      "Scorpio"
    ], 
    "question": "If you were born on Christmas Day, what would your star sign be?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joanne Kathleen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Julia Kathleen", 
      "Joanne Katherine", 
      "Julia Katherine"
    ], 
    "question": "What do the initials \"JK\" stand for in the name \"JK Rowling\", Author of the \"Harry Potter\" books?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One", 
      "Two", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Driver Has Been Disqualified", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Race Has Been Won", 
      "A Driver Has Died", 
      "The Fastest Lap Has Been Set"
    ], 
    "question": "In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sarah Paulson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keira Knightley", 
      "Naomi Watts", 
      "Salma Hayek", 
      "Rachel Weisz", 
      "Frances Fisher", 
      "Kristin Scott Thomas", 
      "Pen\u00e9lope Cruz", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Sally Hawkins"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including American Horror Story and 12 Years a Slave?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which director directed Jurassic Park?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Maldives is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malawi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Gabon"
    ], 
    "question": "Zambia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nicholas Nickleby' was written by which English writer and social critic?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slaughterhouse-Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Clockwork Orange", 
      "Catch-22", 
      "Flatland", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Ulysses", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Animal Farm", 
      "Nineteen Eighty-Four"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1969, which piece of written work starts with the line 'All this happened, more or less.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Peru", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ecuador", 
      "Bolivia", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Panama", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Paraguay"
    ], 
    "question": "In which country is Machu Picchu?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "in ethics, duty", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "concept in anthropology, biology, algebraic topology, and sociology, meaning 'likeness in structure'", 
      "the characteristics of the skull", 
      "blackberries", 
      "butterflies and moths", 
      "the scientific study and cultivation of fruits", 
      "volcanoes and related phenomena", 
      "windmills, watermills and animal engines", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Deontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kajaani", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Vuolijoki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Blues Brothers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sister Act", 
      "National Lampoon's Vacation", 
      "Animal House"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Comedy Film Does Aretha Franklin Star As A Proprietress Of A Soul Food Joint? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Francis Drake", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horatio Nelson", 
      "George Rodney", 
      "John Jervis"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Played Bowls Before Engaging The Spanish Armada?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Macbeth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romeo & Juliette", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "Double, double toil and trouble, Fire burn, and cauldron bubble. Comes from which of Shakespeare's plays?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mercury", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Zinc", 
      "Cadmium", 
      "Lead"
    ], 
    "question": "What is quicksilver also known as?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blackburn Rovers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Manchester United", 
      "Arsenal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which was the second club to win the English Premier League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Julianne Moore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cate Blanchett", 
      "Nicole Kidman", 
      "Natalie Portman", 
      "Kate Winslet", 
      "Helen Mirren", 
      "Maggie Smith", 
      "Charlize Theron", 
      "Sandra B\u00e6 Hovedr", 
      "Kirsten Dunst", 
      "Emma Thompson"
    ], 
    "question": "The films The Big Lebowski and The Hours feature which American actress?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martin Scorsese", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Gangs of New York?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of The Bahamas is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Qatar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Georgia", 
      "Syria", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Israel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Iran?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Enid Blyton", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. K. Rowling", 
      "Virginia Woolf"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
      "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", 
      "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", 
      "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", 
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth", 
      "Eclipse", 
      "An Antarctic Mystery", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City"
    ], 
    "question": "'It was nearing midnight and the Prime Minister was sitting alone in his office, reading a long memo that was slipping through his brain without leaving the lightest trace of meaning behind.' This is the first line of which 2005 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cheyenne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jackson", 
      "Casper", 
      "Laramie"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Wyoming?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the effects of climate on living organisms", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "friction and lubrication", 
      "especially as related to Christianity", 
      "wine and winemaking", 
      "dreams", 
      "the writings and practices of historians", 
      "intonation in speech", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "the same as otolaryngology"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Bioclimatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fujisawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shibuya?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Marathon Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Graduate", 
      "Rain Man", 
      "Tootsie"
    ], 
    "question": "In which 1970's films does Dustin Hoffman play the character ' Babe Levy'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Declaration Of Independence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Constitution", 
      "The Emancipation Procalation", 
      "The Liberty Decree"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 1776 American Affirmation Asserted The Basic Rights Of All?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "Anna Karenina"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does 'Mr. Darcy' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "To Get Insects Below The Bark", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "To attract a mate", 
      "To communicate", 
      "To make a nest"
    ], 
    "question": "Why Does The Woodpecker Peck Wood?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mayfair", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kensington", 
      "Trafalgar Square", 
      "Old Kent Road"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Most Valuble Property In A Game Of British Monopoly?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Danny Trejo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Christian Bale", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Donald Sutherland"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Desperate Housewives and NCIS: Los Angeles feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roman Polanski", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed The Pianist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Tonga is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Montenegro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hungary", 
      "Albania", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Austria", 
      "Italy", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Romania", 
      "Greece", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Poland", 
      "Malta", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Monaco"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Bosnia and Herzegovina?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Joseph Conrad", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "E. T. A. Hoffmann"
    ], 
    "question": "'Oliver Twist' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Sancho Panza' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Hobbit", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Charlotte's Web", 
      "Alice's Adventures in Wonderland", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Jonathan Livingston Seagull", 
      "The Stand", 
      "The City & the City", 
      "The Adventures of Pinocchio", 
      "The Prince and the Pauper"
    ], 
    "question": "'In a hole in the ground there lived a hobbit.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eritrea", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Chad", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Central African Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "_________ is the largest country in Africa. It has a population greater than 28,100,000.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "dialects", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "rays, usually ionising radiation", 
      "drugs", 
      "clouds", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "bryophytes", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "vaccines"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dialectology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Seine?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Frank Capra", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orson Welles", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Howard Hawks"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed the 1946 classic 'It's A Wonderful Life'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mexico", 
      "China", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "In what country did the \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boys", 
      "Witches", 
      "Game"
    ], 
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's _________\".", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Transformer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Resister", 
      "Capacitor", 
      "Micrometer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Electrical Device Can Change The Magnitude Of Voltage Or Current", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "England"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Charlton Heston", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Ben Kingsley", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Ralph Fiennes", 
      "Keanu Reeves"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Ben-Hur and Dynasty?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Schindler's List?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Laos is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ukraine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "India", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Thailand"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Russia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mikhail Sholokhov", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ivan Turgenev", 
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz", 
      "Leo Tolstoy", 
      "Franz Kafka", 
      "Charles Dickens", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Ayn Rand", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Robert E. Howard", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Soviet writer (1905-1984) wrote 'And Quiet Flows the Don'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kidnapped", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer", 
      "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Heidi", 
      "The Count of Monte Cristo", 
      "Bluebeard", 
      "Gargantua and Pantagruel"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1884, which piece of written work starts with the line 'You don\u2019t know about me without you have read a book by the name of The Adventures of Tom Sawyer; but that ain't no matter. That book was made by Mr. Mark Twain, and he told the truth, mainly. There were things which he stretched, but mainly he told the truth. That is nothing. I never seen anybody but lied one time or another, without it was Aunt Polly, or the widow, or maybe Mary.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Singapore", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Taipei", 
      "Kuala Lumpur", 
      "Malacca"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Singapore?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "existence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life", 
      "grasses", 
      "the scientific study of muscles", 
      "history, literature, art and culture of Iran", 
      "rocks", 
      "museum management", 
      "plant diseases", 
      "plankton"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ontology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mexico City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guadalajara", 
      "Monterrey", 
      "M\u00e9rida", 
      "Puebla City", 
      "Tijuana", 
      "Silao Municipality", 
      "Chihuahua City", 
      "Hermosillo", 
      "Le\u00f3n de Los Aldama", 
      "Salinas de Hidalgo, San Luis Potos\u00ed"
    ], 
    "question": "'Tenochtitlan' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Axel Foley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Johnny West", 
      "Marcus Steel", 
      "Jarvis Hansen"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the name of Eddie Murphy's character in Beverly Hills Cop?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Crete", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Babylon", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Turkey"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the ancient script of Linear A and Linear B found?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Twelfth Night", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "The Winter's Tale", 
      "Coriolanus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Shakespearean play refers to the date of epiphany?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Smallpox", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Infuenza", 
      "COVID-19", 
      "Rubella"
    ], 
    "question": "What Vaccine Did Edward Jenner Develop? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Newcastle United", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Arsenal", 
      "Aston Villa"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1992 Kevin Keegan became manager of which football club?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hilary Duff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Olivia Wilde", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Sophia Loren", 
      "Jacqueline Bisset", 
      "Sally Hawkins", 
      "Lucy Lawless", 
      "Carey Mulligan", 
      "Audrey Hepburn", 
      "Catherine Deneuve", 
      "Rani Mukherjee"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American actress and singer has starred in films including Two and a Half Men and Ghost Whisperer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of Schindler's List?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Antigua and Barbuda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Italy", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Germany", 
      "Austria", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Malta", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Spain", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Hungary"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Monaco?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elias L\u00f6nnrot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Astrid Lindgren", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Giovanni Boccaccio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Kalevala' was written by which Finnish physician, philologist and collector of traditional Finnish oral poetry (1802-1884)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voyages Extraordinaires", 
      "Percy Jackson & the Olympians", 
      "Twilight", 
      "The Hunger Games", 
      "His Dark Materials trilogy", 
      "A Song of Ice and Fire", 
      "The Chronicles of Narnia", 
      "canon of Sherlock Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Neville Longbottom appears in which book series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Game of Thrones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Silver Chair", 
      "The Amber Spyglass", 
      "The Wizard of the Emerald City", 
      "The Alchemist", 
      "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone", 
      "The Hobbit", 
      "The Mysterious Island", 
      "Gulliver's Travels"
    ], 
    "question": "Published in 1996, which piece of written work starts with the line '\u201cWe should start back,\u201d Gared urged as the woods began to grow dark around them.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mogadishu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timbuktu", 
      "Bakar", 
      "Addis Ababa"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Somalia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "music in society, usually non-western music", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent", 
      "friction and lubrication", 
      "oceans", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "blackberries", 
      "the theological study of redemption", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "war in an interdisciplinary context"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Ethnomusicology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pieks\u00e4m\u00e4ki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pieks\u00e4nmaa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mrs Robinson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mrs Bouvier", 
      "Mrs Church", 
      "Mrs Sleet"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The Name Of The Character Played By Anne Bancroft In The 1967 Film 'The Graduate'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raoul", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pedro", 
      "Mikel", 
      "Sergio"
    ], 
    "question": "What's fidel castro's brother's name? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tarzan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiderman", 
      "Scooby Doo", 
      "Buggs Bunny"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous character did Edgar Rice Burroughs create?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Feet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antennae", 
      "Nose", 
      "Anus"
    ], 
    "question": "What Does A Butterfly Use To Taste?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matt Bomer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peter Cushing", 
      "Michael Ironside", 
      "Kenneth Branagh", 
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Rowan Atkinson", 
      "Stephen Fry", 
      "Dolph Lundgren", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Richard Burton"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Chuck and Guiding Light?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Lumet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of 12 Angry Men?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Marshall Islands is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Greece", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cyprus", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Romania", 
      "Egypt", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Albania", 
      "Belarus"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkey shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alexandre Dumas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anatole France", 
      "Gustave Flaubert", 
      "Charles Perrault", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "\u00c9mile Zola", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Andr\u00e9 Gide", 
      "Guy de Maupassant", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois-Ren\u00e9 de Chateaubriand", 
      "Victor Hugo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'D'Artagnan Romances'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jane Eyre", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "Little Women", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "Sense and Sensibility", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Atlas Shrugged", 
      "The Red and the Black"
    ], 
    "question": "'There was no possibility of taking a walk that day.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oakland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "San Fransico", 
      "Santa Rosa", 
      "Sacramento", 
      "San Jose", 
      "Reno"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city lies on the east side of San Francisco Bay?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "a dissimilarity of parts often attributable to a difference in origin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "shells and of molluscs", 
      "the age of the Earth", 
      "race", 
      "fermentation", 
      "stalkers", 
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites", 
      "the lymph system and glands", 
      "a branch of medicine that deals with the venous system"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Heterology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "'Seine' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "Bruce Willis spends Christmas fighting terrorists in the 1988 film 'Die Hard'', which American city is this set in", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jarrow March", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Swing Riots", 
      "Tolpuddle Martyrs", 
      "The Chartists"
    ], 
    "question": "What famous protest took place in Britain in 1936?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Satan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jesus", 
      "Dante", 
      "Judas"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is the protagonist of Milton's Paradise Lost?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pelican", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Turtle", 
      "Flamingo", 
      "Tiger"
    ], 
    "question": "A __________ consumes about 33 percent of its body weight in a single meal.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football (American)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Kingsley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Josh Brolin", 
      "Adam Sandler", 
      "Danny DeVito", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Mark Wahlberg", 
      "Brian Cox", 
      "Dwayne Johnson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor's roles include Iron Man 3 and The Jungle Book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the director of A Beautiful Mind?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Seychelles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nigeria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Mali", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Chad"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Benin?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Christopher Tolkien", 
      "Philip Pullman", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Lewis Carroll", 
      "H. G. Wells", 
      "Nick Hornby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets' was written by which British novelist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "In which book does the character 'Lady Catherine de Bourgh' appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sense and Sensibility", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "The Lady of the Camellias", 
      "David Copperfield", 
      "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man", 
      "Candide", 
      "Great Expectations", 
      "Manon Lescaut", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "'The family of Dashwood had been long settled in Sussex.' This is the first line of which 1811 piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arizona/Nevada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "California/Nevada", 
      "Utah/Colorado", 
      "Utah/Nevada"
    ], 
    "question": "On which state border is the Hoover Dam? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "flies", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "schematic layouts", 
      "the study and interpretation of symbols, or a set of symbols", 
      "ligaments", 
      "sacred texts", 
      "sex", 
      "study of devil worshipers", 
      "rocks and the conditions by which they form", 
      "the study and treatment of diseases of the urogenital tract"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Dipterology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Takatsuki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tonda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Reginald Christie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Wayne Gacey Jr", 
      "Ted Bundy", 
      "Ed Gaine"
    ], 
    "question": "Which notorious murderer, hanged in July 1953, had his story told in the film \"Ten Rillington Place\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Falklands War", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Irish War", 
      "The Vietnam War", 
      "The Gibraltan War"
    ], 
    "question": "Which War Involving The UK Began In 1982?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "King Lear", 
      "Julius Caesar", 
      "Othello", 
      "Coriolanus", 
      "Anthony and Cleopatra"
    ], 
    "question": "In which Shakespearean tragedy Does Laertes appear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Virtual Reality", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Augmented Reality", 
      "Visual Hologram", 
      "Immersive Space"
    ], 
    "question": "What 2 Word Term Is Given To A Simulated 3D Environment Used in Computer Graphics? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "15", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "21", 
      "25", 
      "20"
    ], 
    "question": "How many points win a game in badminton?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Christian Bale", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves", 
      "Dan Aykroyd", 
      "Donald Sutherland", 
      "Dwayne Johnson", 
      "G\u00e9rard Depardieu", 
      "Shah Rukh Khan", 
      "Kiefer Sutherland", 
      "Michael Douglas", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Brian Cox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British actor has starred in films including The Dark Knight and Batman Begins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Yates", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows \u2013 Part 1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Togo is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Grenada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Barbados", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Panama", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Cuba"
    ], 
    "question": "Venezuela shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Edgar Allan Poe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Nathaniel Hawthorne", 
      "Mario Puzo", 
      "Dan Brown", 
      "Henry James", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Washington Irving", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Philip K. Dick", 
      "Jack Vance"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American author, poet, editor and literary critic wrote 'Annabel Lee'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pride and Prejudice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fault in Our Stars", 
      "Ship of Fools", 
      "War and Peace", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Jane Eyre", 
      "Taras Bulba", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "Lady Catherine de Bourgh appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gone with the Wind", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Fall of the King", 
      "All Quiet on the Western Front", 
      "A Tale of Two Cities", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "The Name of the Rose", 
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas", 
      "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell", 
      "The Kreutzer Sonata"
    ], 
    "question": "'Scarlett O\u2019Hara was not beautiful, but men seldom realized it when caught by her charm as the Tarleton twins were.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tripoli", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Benghazi", 
      "Tunis", 
      "Alexandria"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Libya?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "algae", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen", 
      "handwriting for the purpose of analysing the character of the writer", 
      "or biogeomorphology, interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes", 
      "study of horses", 
      "the phylum Bryozoa", 
      "illness", 
      "a more inclusive term for theology", 
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Phycology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ichikawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Gy\u014dtoku' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hugh Grant", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Colin Firth", 
      "Liam Neeson", 
      "Alan Rickman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who plays the role of the Prime Minister, in the 2003 Christmas film 'Love Actually''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dog", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Horse", 
      "Goat", 
      "Ghost"
    ], 
    "question": "The only __________ to ever appear in a Shakespearean play was Crab in \"The Two Gentlemen of Verona.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "hours", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "days", 
      "minutes", 
      "nights"
    ], 
    "question": "The snail mates only once in its entire life. When it does mate, however, it may take as long as 12 _______ to consummate the act.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "Three", 
      "Four"
    ], 
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bruce Willis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Robert De Niro", 
      "Samuel L. Jackson", 
      "Liam Neeson", 
      "William Shatner", 
      "Christopher Lee", 
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger", 
      "Tom Hanks", 
      "Anthony Hopkins", 
      "Ewan McGregor", 
      "Gary Oldman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Sin City and Ally McBeal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tim Burton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Batman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Lucia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Luxembourg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Italy", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Sweden", 
      "Andorra"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Germany?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jostein Gaarder", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "G. K. Chesterton", 
      "Jules Verne", 
      "J. R. R. Tolkien", 
      "Alphonse Daudet", 
      "Victor Hugo", 
      "Walter Scott", 
      "Oscar Wilde", 
      "Miguel de Cervantes", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft"
    ], 
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Sophie's World'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Poland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country borders Italy, Switzerland, Germany, Czech Republic, Hungary, Slovenia, and Liechtenstein?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "life in outer space", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "prehistoric people and human origins", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension", 
      "the signification and application of words", 
      "fungus + -ology, see mycology", 
      "the age of trees and the records in their rings", 
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees", 
      "the same as otolaryngology", 
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Exobiology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nagaoka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nagaokahon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Khrushchev", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Putin", 
      "Gorbachev", 
      "Lenin"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1953, Stalin Died. Who ultimately succeeded him as the leader of the Soviet Union?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "As You Like It", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Twelfth Night", 
      "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 
      "Richard III"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Shakespearean play is set in the forest of Arden?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jupiter", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Venus", 
      "Neptune", 
      "Saturn"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the largest planet in the solar system.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wimbledon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Olympics", 
      "The World CUP Final", 
      "The FA Cup Final"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Sporting Event Was BBC2's First Ever Colour Tranmission In 1967?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mark Hamill", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alan Cumming", 
      "Richard Burton", 
      "Tim Curry", 
      "Peter O'Toole", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Jet Li", 
      "Luke Evans", 
      "Stephen Fry", 
      "Kenneth Branagh", 
      "Michael Ironside"
    ], 
    "question": "The films Criminal Minds and Star Wars feature which actor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Lumet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg", 
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed 12 Angry Men?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Andorra is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Chile", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Brazil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "George R. R. Martin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen King", 
      "Jack Vance", 
      "Edgar Rice Burroughs", 
      "Robert A. Heinlein", 
      "H. P. Lovecraft", 
      "Ursula K. Le Guin", 
      "C. S. Lewis", 
      "Neil Gaiman", 
      "Isaac Asimov", 
      "Philip K. Dick"
    ], 
    "question": "'A Game of Thrones' was written by which author?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don Quixote", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Diary of a Chambermaid", 
      "The Neverending Story", 
      "Orlando Furioso", 
      "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", 
      "Foucault's Pendulum", 
      "Ready Player One", 
      "Robinson Crusoe", 
      "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
    ], 
    "question": "The character 'Sancho Panza' appears in which book?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Silmarillion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Decameron", 
      "Dead Souls", 
      "Welcome to the N.H.K.", 
      "Justine", 
      "The Magic Mountain", 
      "The Good Soldier \u0160vejk", 
      "Anna Karenina", 
      "The Great Gatsby"
    ], 
    "question": "'There was Eru, the One, who in Arda is called Il\u00favatar; and he made first the Ainur, the Holy Ones, that were the offspring of his thought, and they were with him before aught else was made.' This is the first line of which piece of written work?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cuba", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Will You Find The Bay Of Pigs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "diseases and the care of newborn infants; a branch of pediatrics/paediatrics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "a book by Leibniz on his theory of monads", 
      "numbers", 
      "movement in relation to human anatomy; a branch of medicine", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "the atmosphere", 
      "male health and disease", 
      "sleep", 
      "bryophytes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Neonatology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tokyo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "'Edo' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Baby Ruth candy bar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Smores", 
      "A Twinky", 
      "A Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the person chained to wall in Goonies want?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "1533", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1633", 
      "1733", 
      "1433"
    ], 
    "question": "In What Year Was Queen Elizabeth The I Born?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Van Gogh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salvador Dali", 
      "Andy Warhol", 
      "Raphael", 
      "Vermeer"
    ], 
    "question": "Which painter reputedly cut of his own ear?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "How many beams of light are used to record a holograph?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Crews", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Richard Harris", 
      "Anthony Quinn", 
      "Hugo Weaving", 
      "Toshir\u014d Mifune", 
      "Warwick Davis", 
      "Timothy Spall", 
      "Simon Pegg", 
      "Tim Roth", 
      "Roger Moore", 
      "Peter O'Toole"
    ], 
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Brooklyn Nine-Nine and Terminator Salvation?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steven Spielberg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Woody Allen", 
      "Martin Scorsese", 
      "Alfred Hitchcock", 
      "Ridley Scott", 
      "Ron Howard", 
      "Akira Kurosawa", 
      "Stanley Kubrick", 
      "Ingmar Bergman", 
      "Billy Wilder", 
      "Federico Fellini", 
      "Michael Bay", 
      "Richard Donner", 
      "John Huston", 
      "Robert Wise", 
      "Tim Burton", 
      "Quentin Tarantino", 
      "Peter Jackson", 
      "William Wyler", 
      "Christopher Nolan", 
      "Elia Kazan", 
      "Roman Polanski", 
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut", 
      "Roland Emmerich", 
      "Blake Edwards", 
      "Clint Eastwood", 
      "Fred Zinnemann", 
      "Bryan Singer", 
      "David Yates", 
      "Richard Fleischer", 
      "Alan Parker", 
      "James Cameron", 
      "Robert Zemeckis", 
      "Sidney Lumet", 
      "Robert Rodriguez", 
      "Francis Ford Coppola", 
      "George Lucas", 
      "Oliver Stone", 
      "Chris Columbus", 
      "Luchino Visconti", 
      "John Carpenter", 
      "David Lean", 
      "J. Lee Thompson", 
      "Pier Paolo Pasolini", 
      "Luc Besson", 
      "Sergio Leone", 
      "Wolfgang Petersen", 
      "Sydney Pollack", 
      "John Ford", 
      "Barry Sonnenfeld", 
      "Steven Soderbergh", 
      "Stanley Donen", 
      "Howard Hawks", 
      "David Lynch", 
      "Zack Snyder", 
      "Sam Raimi", 
      "Vittorio De Sica", 
      "John Sturges", 
      "John Glen", 
      "Luis Bu\u00f1uel", 
      "David Fincher", 
      "Sylvester Stallone", 
      "Paul W. S. Anderson", 
      "Guy Hamilton", 
      "Jean Girault", 
      "Otto Preminger", 
      "Terry Gilliam", 
      "Robert Bresson", 
      "Sam Mendes", 
      "Brian De Palma", 
      "Danny Boyle", 
      "Mel Brooks", 
      "Franklin J. Schaffner", 
      "Stanley Kramer", 
      "Bernardo Bertolucci", 
      "John G. Avildsen", 
      "Tony Scott", 
      "Andrei Tarkovsky", 
      "George Roy Hill", 
      "Joel Schumacher", 
      "Robert Altman", 
      "Richard Lester", 
      "Joshua Logan", 
      "Joseph L. Mankiewicz", 
      "Baz Luhrmann", 
      "Michelangelo Antonioni", 
      "Robert Aldrich", 
      "Justin Lin", 
      "M. Night Shyamalan", 
      "Jean-Luc Godard", 
      "Joel Coen", 
      "Terence Young", 
      "Roger Corman", 
      "Anthony Russo", 
      "Sam Peckinpah", 
      "Ang Lee", 
      "Jean-Jacques Annaud", 
      "John Badham", 
      "Lewis Gilbert", 
      "Tom Shadyac", 
      "Jay Roach", 
      "Milo\u0161 Forman", 
      "Guy Ritchie", 
      "John McTiernan", 
      "Peter Weir", 
      "Vincente Minnelli", 
      "Peyton Reed", 
      "J. J. Abrams", 
      "George Stevens", 
      "William Friedkin", 
      "Mike Nichols", 
      "Paul Verhoeven", 
      "Jon Favreau", 
      "Stephen Sommers", 
      "Brett Ratner", 
      "Paul Greengrass", 
      "Charles Walters", 
      "Joss Whedon", 
      "Satyajit Ray", 
      "Leonid Gaidai", 
      "Guillermo del Toro", 
      "Richard Brooks", 
      "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", 
      "Chris Weitz", 
      "Don Siegel", 
      "Norman Jewison", 
      "John Landis", 
      "Terence Fisher", 
      "Joe Wright", 
      "Werner Herzog", 
      "Irvin Kershner", 
      "Lars von Trier", 
      "Hal Ashby", 
      "Henry Hathaway", 
      "Herbert Ross", 
      "Anthony Mann", 
      "John Woo", 
      "Krzysztof Kie\u015blowski", 
      "Darren Aronofsky", 
      "Wes Craven", 
      "Jean-Pierre Melville", 
      "Lilly Wachowski", 
      "Mike Newell", 
      "Mel Gibson", 
      "Bob Fosse", 
      "Martin Campbell", 
      "Louis Leterrier", 
      "George Cukor", 
      "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu", 
      "Leonard Nimoy", 
      "Gus Van Sant", 
      "Michael Haneke", 
      "Nicholas Meyer", 
      "James Gunn", 
      "Raja Gosnell", 
      "Warren Beatty", 
      "Louis Malle", 
      "Arthur Penn", 
      "Henry King", 
      "McG", 
      "Alan J. Pakula", 
      "Barry Levinson", 
      "George Miller", 
      "Kevin Costner", 
      "Brad Bird", 
      "John Schlesinger", 
      "Charlie Chaplin", 
      "Ishir\u014d Honda", 
      "John Boorman", 
      "Russell Mulcahy", 
      "Mervyn LeRoy", 
      "Franco Zeffirelli", 
      "Martin Brest", 
      "Jan de Bont", 
      "Michael Apted", 
      "Rob Cohen", 
      "Henri-Georges Clouzot", 
      "Roland Joff\u00e9", 
      "Jon Watts", 
      "Nicholas Ray", 
      "Sean S. Cunningham", 
      "Matthew Vaughn", 
      "Daniel Mann", 
      "Michael Cimino", 
      "Andrzej Wajda", 
      "Bobby Farrelly", 
      "Peter Bogdanovich", 
      "Mario Monicelli", 
      "James Mangold", 
      "Roberto Rossellini", 
      "Mark Robson", 
      "Henry Koster", 
      "Richard Thorpe", 
      "Kenji Mizoguchi", 
      "Ren\u00e9 Cl\u00e9ment", 
      "Orson Welles", 
      "Renny Harlin", 
      "Adrian Lyne", 
      "Martin Ritt", 
      "Damien Chazelle", 
      "Todd Phillips", 
      "James Wan", 
      "Hal Needham", 
      "Francis Lawrence", 
      "Dario Argento", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Jim Jarmusch", 
      "Gore Verbinski", 
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder", 
      "Simon West", 
      "Kevin Smith", 
      "Darren Lynn Bousman", 
      "Michael Mann", 
      "Ken Loach", 
      "Matt Reeves", 
      "Ben Stiller", 
      "Joe Dante", 
      "Phillip Noyce", 
      "Len Wiseman"
    ], 
    "question": "Who directed Schindler's List?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Maldives is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Suriname", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Panama", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Peru", 
      "Bolivia", 
      "The Bahamas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guyana?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dante Alighieri", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Giovanni Boccaccio", 
      "Agatha Christie", 
      "Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn", 
      "Natsuo Kirino", 
      "Haruki Murakami", 
      "Charlotte Bront\u00eb", 
      "Michael Crichton", 
      "Robert Jordan", 
      "Charles Darwin", 
      "Francisco Quevedo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Italian poet wrote 'Paradiso'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wuthering Heights", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Shining", 
      "The Phantom of the Opera", 
      "Coraline", 
      "Carmilla", 
      "The Picture of Dorian Gray", 
      "Frankenstein", 
      "'Salem's Lot", 
      "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde"
    ], 
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line '1801\u2014I have just returned from a visit to my landlord\u2014the solitary neighbour that I shall be troubled with.'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Denver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "the study or exploration of caves", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "how to encrypt and decrypt secret messages", 
      "methods", 
      "methods", 
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms", 
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions", 
      "glaciers", 
      "cancer", 
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes"
    ], 
    "question": "What is Speleology the study of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chongqing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin", 
      "Wuhan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Chungking?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Film and TV", 
    "correctAnswer": "Old Time Rock & Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rock Around the Clock", 
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Don't Stop Believing"
    ], 
    "question": "In The Film Risky Business Tom Cruise Danced Around His Living Room In His Underpants To What Song", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "History", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ming", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qin", 
      "Han", 
      "Tang"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Chinese dynasty lasted from 1368 to 1644?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Art and Literature", 
    "correctAnswer": "Macbeth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romeo & Juliette", 
      "Hamlet", 
      "King Lear"
    ], 
    "question": "Double, double toil and trouble, Fire burn, and cauldron bubble. Comes from which of Shakespeare's plays?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Science", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pascal", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Borland", 
      "Newton", 
      "Ohm"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The SI Unit Of Pressure", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jack", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Nightmare", 
      "The Flush", 
      "The Drone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The White Ball In A Game Of Bowls?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
